<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="plugin.audio.listenliveeu"
  version="1.1.5"
  name="ListenLiveEU"
  provider-name="bootsy, xycl">
  <requires>
   <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
    library="default.py">
   <provides>audio</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="be">European radio stations streaming live on the internet</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Estacions de ràdios per Internet europees en directe</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Europæiske radiostationer, som streamer live på nettet</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Europäische Radiostationen, die live im Internet streamen</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Ευρωπαϊκοί ραδιοφωνικοί σταθμοί που εκπέμπουν ζωντανά στο διαδίκτυο</summary>
    <summary lang="en">European radio stations streaming live on the internet</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Estaciones de radio europeas retransmitiendo en directo por internet</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Stations de radio européennes en streaming direct depuis internet </summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Stations de radio européenne en direct sur ​​Internet</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Emisoras de radio europeas transmitindo en directo por internet</summary>
    <summary lang="he">שידורי תחנות רדיו אירופאיות חיים באינטרנט.</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Europske radio stanice emitirane uživo sa Interneta</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Európai internetes rádiók</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Le stazioni radio Europee in streaming dal vivo su internet</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Internet live streams van Europese radio stations</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Europejskie stacje radiowe na żywo w internecie</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Estações de rádio europeias com transmissão ao vivo na internet</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Estações de rádio europeias ao vivo por transmissão online</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Európske rádio stanice naživo stramujúce na internete</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Europeiska radiostationer som sänder direkt över internet</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">互联网上的欧洲电台直播流</summary>
    <description lang="be">Welcome to listenlive.eu, a web radio directory showcasing over 4000 radio stations from across Europe streaming live on the internet.</description>
    <description lang="ca">Benvingut a listenlive.eu, un directori de ràdios web amb més de 4000 estacions de tota Europa transmetent en directe per Internet.</description>
    <description lang="da">Velkommen til listenlive.eu, en webradio-oversigt med over 4000 radiostationer fra overalt i Europe, som streamer live på nettet.</description>
    <description lang="de">Listenlive.eu ist ein Web-Radio Aggregator mit mehr als 4000 Radiostationen aus Europa.</description>
    <description lang="el">Καλώς ήρθατε στο listenlive.eu, ένα ευρετήριο διαδικτυακών ραδιοφωνικών σταθμών με περισσότερους από 4000 σταθμούς που εκπέμπουν ζωντανά στο διαδίκτυο σε όλη την Ευρώπη.</description>
    <description lang="en">Welcome to listenlive.eu, a web radio directory showcasing over 4000 radio stations from across Europe streaming live on the internet.</description>
    <description lang="es">Bienvenido a listenlive.eu, una guía de radios online con más de 4000 estaciones de radio de toda Europa retransmitiendo en directo por internet.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Bienvenue à listenlive.eu, un répertoire de web radio réunissant plus de 4000 stations radio depuis toute l'Europe en streaming direct depuis internet.  </description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Bienvenue à listenlive.eu, un répertoire de radio sur le web mettant en valeur plus de 4000 stations radio à travers l'europe en direct sur l'internet.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Benvido a listenlive.eu, unha guía de radios en liña con máis de 4000 emisoras de radio de toda Europa transmitindo en directo por internet.</description>
    <description lang="he">ברוך הבא אל  listenlive.eu, מדריך תחנות רדיו מקוונות המציע יותר מ-4000 תחנות רדיו מכל רחבי אירופה המזרימות שידור חי באינטרנט.</description>
    <description lang="hr">Dobrodošli na listenlive.eu, web radio popis koji prikazuje preko 4000 radio postaja iz cijele Europe emitiranih uživo sa Interneta.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A listenlive.eu több mint 4000 élo rádióadást tartalmaz Európából, melyeket az interneten keresztül érhetsz el.</description>
    <description lang="it">Benvenuto a listenlive.eu una web radio che mostra più di 4000 radio stazioni provenienti da tutta Europa in diretta streaming  su internet.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Welkom bij listenlive.eu, een web radio station met meer dan 4000 radio stations uit heel europa welke live streamen op het internet.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Witamy w listenlive.eu, katalogu ponad 4000 stacji radiowych z całej Europy nadających na żywo w internecie.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Benvindo a listenlive.eu, um directório de rádios web que oferece mais de 4000 estações de rádio de toda a Europa com transmissão ao vivo na internet.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Bem-vindo à listenlive.eu, um diretório de rádio na web que contém mais de 4000 estações de rádio de toda a Europa ao vivo pela internet.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Vitajte na listenlive.eu, web stránke, ktorá prezentuje vyše 4000 rádio staníc z celej Európy streamujúcich naživo na internete.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Välkommen till listenlive.eu, en webbradiokatalog med över 4000 radiostationer från över hela Europa som sänder direkt över internet.</description>
    <description lang="zh">欢迎来到 listenlive.eu，一个包含超过4000个欧洲电台直播流的网络电台目录。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language></language>
  </extension>
</addon>
