<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.xperience-more" version="2.0.4" name="Xperience More" provider-name="Nessus">
  <requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0" />
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.19"/>
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="4.0.7"/>
		<import addon="script.tvtunes" version="3.0.1" />
		<import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="5.0.4"/>
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="12.0.11" />
		<import addon="script.globalsearch" version="1.1.0" />
		<import addon="script.artistslideshow" version="1.4.6" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="0.75" debugging="false">
	    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p"/>
	</extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="de">Xperience More von Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Xperience More από τον Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Xperience More by Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Xperience More by Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Xperience More by Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Xperience More por Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Xperience More par Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Xpérience plus par Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Xperience More por Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Xperience More Nessustól</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Xperience More di Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Xperience More by Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Xperience More, sukurta Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Xperience More oleh Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Xperience More door Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Xperience More autorstwa Nessusa</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Xperience More de Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Xperience More por Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Xperience More, автор Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Xperience More av Nessus</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">Xperience More 由 Nessus 开发</summary>
    <description lang="de">Xperience More ist eine aktualisierte und erweiterte Version des Xperience Designs von Team Blackbolt und umfasst die aktuellsten Funktionen, sofern diese in das ursprüngliche Designkonzept passen.</description>
    <description lang="el">Το Xperience More είναι μια ενημερωμένη και αναβαθμισμένη έκδοση του κελύφους Xperience από την Team Blackbolt, με όλες τις πρόσφατες προσθήκες του Kodi που ταιριάζουν με τον αρχικό σχεδιασμό του κελύφους.</description>
    <description lang="en">Xperience More is an updated and upgraded version of the Xperience skin by Team Blackbolt to all the latest features of Kodi as long as they fit in skin's original design.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Xperience More is an updated and upgraded version of the Xperience skin by Team Blackbolt to all the latest features of Kodi as long as they fit in skin's original design.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Xperience More is an updated and upgraded version of the Xperience skin by Team Blackbolt to all the latest features of Kodi as long as they fit in skin's original design.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Xperience More est une version mise à jour et améliorée du thème Xperience de la Team Blackbolt. Il intégre toutes les dernières fonctionnalités de Kodi tant qu'elles peuvent être adaptées dans le design original du thème.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Xpérience plus est un version améliorée de l'habillage Xpérience par l'équipe Blackbolt mise à niveau vers toutes les dernières fonctions de Kodi, tant qu'elles s’intègrent dans la conception originale de l'habillage.</description>
    <description lang="gl">Xperience More é unha versión actualizada e mellorada do tema Xperience do Equipo Blackbolt, soporta todas as últimas características do Kodi sempre e cando se axuste ao deseño orixinal do tema.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Az Xperience More egy frissített/kiegészített Xperience (Team Blackbolt) felszín a legújabb funkciókkal, mely hű maradt az eredeti design-hoz.</description>
    <description lang="it">Xperience More è una versione aggiornata ed upgradata dello skin Xperience del Team Blackbolt a tutte le ultime funzionalità di Kodi in modo da calzare nel design originale.</description>
    <description lang="ko">Xperience More 스킨은 Team Blackbolt가 제작한 Xperience 스킨의 원 디자인을 유지하면서 최신 Kodi 기능으로 업데이트하여 업그레이드한 스킨입니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Xperience More yra atnaujinta ir patobulinta Xperience teminės išvaizdos, kurią sukūrė Blackbolt, versija, į kurią įtrauktos visos naujausios Kodi savybės, jei tik jos atitinka originalų teminės išvaizdos dizainą.</description>
    <description lang="ms">Xperience More merupakan versi dikemaskini dan ditatar dari kulit Xperience oleh Pasukan Blackbolt melibatkan semua fitur terkini Kodi yang mana ia menepati rekabentuk kulit yang asal.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Xperience More is een geupdate en geupgrade versie van de Xperience skin door Team Blackbolt naar de laatste toevoegingen aan Kodi zolang als de toevoegingen in de originele skin passen.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Xperience More jest zaktualizowaną wersją skóry Xperience utworzonej przez Team Blackbolt by zawierała wszystkie najnowsze funkcjonalności Kodi, jeśli tylko odpowiadają one oryginalnemu wyglądowi skóry.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Xperience More é uma versão actualizada e melhorada do tema Xperience, da Team Blackbolt, que suporta todas as últimas funcionalidades do Kodi, desde que tenham lugar na estrutura original do tema.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Xperience More é uma atualização da versão da skin Xperience do Team Blackbolt com todos os recursos atuais do Kodi desde que se encaixem no desenho original da skin.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Xperience More это продвинутая версия обложки Xperience (авт. Team Blackbolt), которая позволяет использовать многочисленные новые возможности Kodi, если они не противоречат идее дизайна обложки.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Xperience More är en version av Xperience-skalet av Team Blackbolt som blivit uppdaterat och uppgraderat till att stödja de senaste funktionerna i Kodi, om de passar in i skalets ursprungliga design.</description>
    <description lang="zh">Xperience More是Team Blackbolt开发的更新升级版本, 包含最新的Kodi的特性, 并且符合皮肤的原有设计.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="bg">Не се поддържа ползването на мишка</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de">Maus nicht unterstützt</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el">Δεν υποστηρίζεται η χρήση ποντικιού.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">Mouse usage not supported.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Mouse usage not supported.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_US">Mouse usage not supported.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es">El uso de ratón no esta soportado</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">L'utilisation de la souris n'est pas supportée.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">L'utilisation de la souris n'est pas prise en charge</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="gl">Uso do rato non soportado</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">Az Egér használata nem támogatott</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">Mouse non supportato</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">마우스 사용은 지원하지 않습니다.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt">Pelės naudojimas nepalaikomas.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ms">Penggunaan tetikus tidak disokong.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl">Het gebruik van een muis wordt niet ondersteund</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">Mysz nie jest obsługiwana</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Não é possível utilizar o rato.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Mouse não suportado</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru">Использование мыши не поддерживается</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv">Musanvändning stöds ej.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">不支持使用鼠标.</disclaimer>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
