<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
    id="skin.arctic.zephyr"
    version="2.0.8"
    name="Arctic: Zephyr"
    provider-name="jurialmunkey">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.9.0"/>
        <import addon="script.skinshortcuts" version="0.4.0"/>
        <import addon="service.library.data.provider" version="0.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.extendedinfo" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.globalsearch" version="5.0.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
    debugging="false"
    effectslowdown="1">
        <res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" />
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="cs">Čistý, minimální, elegantní, jednoduchý, lehký.</summary>
        <summary lang="de">Klar, minimalistisch, elegant, einfach, leicht</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_AU">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_NZ">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">Clean, minimal, elegant, simple, light.</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Limpio, minimalista, elegante, simple, ligero.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Clair, minimaliste, élégant, simple et léger.</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">Net, minimal, élégant, simple, léger.</summary>
        <summary lang="it">Pulita, minima, elegante, semplice, leggera</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">Švari, minimali, elegantiška, paprasta, lengva.</summary>
        <summary lang="ms">Kemas, minimal, elegan, ringkas, pantas.</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Zuiver, minimalistisch, elegant, simpel, licht.</summary>
        <summary lang="no">Rent, minimalt, elegant, enkelt, lett.</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Prosta, minimalista, elegancka i lekka</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Limpa, simplista, elegante, leve.</summary>
        <summary lang="ro">Curat, minimalist, elegant, simplu, ușor</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Опрятный, минималистичный, элегантный, простой, светлый.</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Ren, minimal, elegant, simpel, lätt</summary>
        <summary lang="tr">Temiz, minimal, şık, sade, hafif</summary>
        <description lang="de">Arctic: Zephyr ist die dritte Iteration des Arctic Skins von jurialmunkey und ein minimalistisches, klares und simples Interface für deine Medien mit dem gewissen Etwas.</description>
        <description lang="en">Arctic: Zephyr is the third iteration of the Arctic skin created by jurialmunkey. Arctic focuses on being simple, clean and minimalistic with a light spin.</description>
        <description lang="en_AU">Arctic: Zephyr is the third iteration of the Arctic skin created by jurialmunkey. Arctic focuses on being simple, clean and minimalistic with a light spin.</description>
        <description lang="en_NZ">Arctic: Zephyr is the third iteration of the Arctic skin created by jurialmunkey. Arctic focuses on being simple, clean and minimalistic with a light spin.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">Arctic: Zephyr is the third iteration of the Arctic skin created by jurialmunkey. Arctic focuses on being simple, clean and minimalistic with a light spin.</description>
        <description lang="es">Arctic: Zephyr es la tercera versión de Arctic skin creada por jurialmunkey. La skin Arctic se centra en ser simple, limplia y minimalista con un toque de luminosidad.</description>
        <description lang="fr">Arctic : Zephyr est la troisième version de l'habillage Arctic créé par jurialmunkey. Arctic se veut simple, net et minimaliste en étant léger.</description>
        <description lang="fr_CA">Arctique : Zéphyr est la troisième version de l'habillage Arctique créé par jurialmunkey. Arctique se veut être simple, net et minimaliste tout en étant léger. </description>
        <description lang="it">Arctic: Zephyr è la terza iterazione della skin Arctic creata da jurialmunkey. Arctic si concentra nell'essere semplice, pulita e minimalistica con delle modifiche.</description>
        <description lang="lt">Arctic: Zephyr yra trečia Arctic teminės išvaizdos, kurios autorius yra jurialmunkey, iteracija. Arctic sutelkia dėmesį ties paprastumu, švarumu ir minimalizmu su lengvu veikimu.</description>
        <description lang="ms">Arctic: Zephyr merupakan iterasi ketiga kulit Arctic yang dihasilkan oleh jurialmunkey. Arctic berfokuskan pada ringkas, kemas dan minimalis dengan sedikit penyuaian.</description>
        <description lang="nl">Arctic: Zephyr is de derde versie van de Arctic skin gecreëerd door jurialmunkey. Arctic focust zich op eenvoudigheid, schoonheid en minimalisme met een lichte twist.</description>
        <description lang="no">Arctic: Zephyr er den tredje iterasjonen av Arctic skallet som ble laget av jurialmunkey. Arctic fokuserer på å være enkel, rent og minimalistisk med et snev av letthet.</description>
        <description lang="pl">Arctic: Zephyr jest trzecią wersją oryginalnej skóry Arctic stworzonej przez jurialmunkey. Arctic skupia się na prostocie i minimalizmie z lekką dozą szaleństwa.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Arctic: Zephyr é a terceira iteração da interface Arctic criada por jurialmunkey. Arctic foi criada para ser simples, limpa e minimalistica.</description>
        <description lang="ru">Arctic: Zephyr это третий виток обложки Arctic, созданной jurialmunkey. Arctic старается быть простой, опрятной и минималистичной.</description>
        <description lang="sv">Arctic: Zephyr är tredje generationen av Arctic skinnet, skapat av jurialmunkey. Arctic fokuserar på att vara enkelt, rent och minimalistiskt med en lätt spinn.</description>
        <description lang="tr">Arctic: Zephyr jurialmunkey tarafından yaratılan Arctic temasının üçüncü yenilemesidir. Arctic teması sade, temiz ve minimalistik olmaya odaklanmıştır.</description>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>
