<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.mediastream_redux"
  version="2.5.1"
  name="MediaStream Redux"
  provider-name="Jezz_X (graphics by team razorfish)">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
    debugging="false"
    effectslowdown="1.0">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="ca">Redisseny de Jezz_X de la pell original "MediaStream"</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Jezz_X's redesign von dem originalen "MediaStream"-Skin</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Επανασχεδιασμός του πρωτότυπου κελύφους MediaStream από τον Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Jezz_X's redesign of the original "MediaStream" skin</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Jezz_X's redesign of the original "MediaStream" skin</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage MediaStream original modifié par Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Redeseño do tema orixinal "MediaStream" por Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Jezz_X által újragondolt "MediaStream" felszín</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">오리지널 "MediaStream"을  Jezz_X가 다시 디자인한 스킨</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Jezz_X's mereka semula kulis asal "MediaStream"</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Jezz_X`s herontwerp van de originele "mediastream" ontwerp</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">MediaStream Redux, o reinventar do tema 'MediaStream' por Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Дополнение текста песен</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Jezz_X's omdesign av det första "MediaStream" skalet</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">"MediaStream" görünümünün Jezz_X tarafından yeniden düzenlenmiş halidir</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">Jezz_X对原“MediaStream”皮肤的重制版</summary>
    <description lang="de">MediaStream Redux ist eine komplettes Remake von grund auf vom Team Razorfish's MediaStream Skin und es benutzt nur die orginalen Skingrafiken (wieauch das Layout des Hauptbildschirmes und einge deren Ansichten) und es ist auch nur für 16x9 und nicht 4x3 so wie das Original.[CR]   Ich habe diese Skin gemacht, weil ich bei dem Mayhem Skin projekt mitgearbeitet habe und ich liebte das orginale Mediastream Skin Design aber die Navigation was sehr umständlich (alte Gewohnheiten sterben nur langsam). Somit ist die Navigation von diesem Skin mehr wie die des PM Skins(Das Menü ist auf der linken Seite)[CR]. Aller Dank gilt dem Team Razorfish für das originale Konzept und die Grafiken die ich in dieser Version verwendet habe</description>
    <description lang="el">Το MediaStream Redux είναι επανασχεδιασμός από την αρχή του κελύφους MediaStream της ομάδας Team Razorfish, που χρησιμοποιεί μόνο τις εικόνες του αρχικού κελύφους (επίσης, τη διαμόρφωση της αρχικής οθόνης του και κάποιους τύπους προβολής) και είναι μόνο για οθόνες 16x9, όχι 4x3 όπως το πρωτότυπο.[CR]   Δημιούργησα αυτό το κέλυφος διότι προερχόμενος από κελύφη όπως το Project Mayhem λάτρεψα τη όψη του πρωτότυπου Mediastream, αλλά βρήκα ότι ήταν πολύ δύσκολο να περιηγηθώ σε αυτό όπως ήθελα (παλιά χούγια). Συνεπώς αυτό το κέλυφος έχει πλοήγηση παρόμοια με τα κελύφη PM (Το μενού είναι στην αριστερή πλευρά)[CR]  Πολλές ευχαριστίες στην Team Razorfish για το αρχικό σχέδιο και τα γραφικά που χρησιμοποιήθηκαν σε αυτήν την έκδοση</description>
    <description lang="en">   MediaStream Redux is a complete remake from the ground up of Team Razorfish's MediaStream skin and only uses the original skins graphics (also its home window layout and some of its views) and is for 16x9 only no 4x3 support like the original.[CR]   I made this skin because coming from the Project Mayhem skins I loved the original Mediastream skin looks but found it very hard to navigate my way around in the original (old habits die hard). So this skin Navigates more like the PM skins (Menu is on the left hand side)[CR]  All credit to Team Razorfish for the original concept and graphics used in this version</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">MediaStream Redux est une toute nouvelle version de l'habillage MediaStream par Razorfish, qui n'utilise que le graphisme de l'habillage original (ainsi que la disposition de sa fenêtre d'accueil et certaines de ses vues) et seulement pour le 16:9 sans prendre en charge le 4:3 comme l'original.[CR]J'ai créé cet habillage car, après les habillages du Projet Mayhem, j'aimais le style de l'habillage MediaStream original, mais trouvais la navigation très difficile (les vieilles habitudes ont la vie dure). Ainsi la navigation se rapproches des habillages du Projet Mayhem (le menu est à gauche).[CR]Le crédit revient à l'équipe Razorfish pour la conception originale et le graphisme utilisés dans cette version.</description>
    <description lang="gl">MediaStream Redux está feito de novo a partir do tema MeadStream do equipo de Razorfish no que se fai uso dalguns gráficos e organización de vistas do tema orixinal, só para pantallas 16x9.[CR]Desenvolvín este tema baseándome nos termos dos temas do Project Mayhem. Gustábame o tema Mediastream orixinal pero atopaba que a navegación polos menús era moi complicada, así que a navegación neste tema é máis semellante á do tema PM (o menú está a mán esquerda)[CR]Todos os créditos van para o equipo de Razorfish polo concepto orixinal e os gráficos usados nesta versión.</description>
    <description lang="hu">A MediaStream Redux egy alapoktól újraírt MediaStream (Team Razorfish) felszín, melyben csak azok a részek maradtak érintetlenül amik az eredeti felszínben kifogástalanul működtek. A Redux immár a 16x9-es képarányt támogatja, ellentétben az eredeti felszín 4x3-as képarányával.[CR]A Redux-ban megváltozott a navigáció, ami az eredeti felszínben gondot okozott. Minden grafikai elem és koncepció a Team Razorfish által készített, eredeti felszínből készült.</description>
    <description lang="ko">   MediaStream Redux는 Team Razorfish의 MediaStream 스킨의 원래 그래픽(과 홈 윈도우 구성, 보기 방식등)만을 사용하고 완전히 처음부터 다시 만든 스킨입니다. 오리지널과 마찬가지로 16:9 전용이며 4x3은 지원하지 않습니다.[CR]   이 스킨을 만든 이유는 Project Mayhem 스킨에서 넘어온 탓에 오리지널 MediStream 스킨의 모양새는 좋았지만 스킨을 사용하기에는 굉장히 불편했기 때문입니다.(오래된 버릇은 쉽게 없어지지 않습습니다.) 그래서 이 스킨의 탐색 방식은 Projetc Mayhem 스킨과 비슷(메뉴가 왼쪽에 있음)합니다.[CR]  All credit to Team Razorfish for the original concept and graphics used in this version</description>
    <description lang="ms">MediaStream Redux ialah pembuatan semula yang lengkap dari asas kulit MediaStream pasukan Razorfish dan hanya gunakan grafik kulit asal (juga bentangan tetingkap rumah dan beberapa antaramukanya) dan hanya untuk 16x9 sahaja dan bukan sokongan 4x3 seperti yang asal.[CR] Saya menghasilkan kulit ini kerana ia berasal dari kulit Project Mayhem dan menyukai penampilan kulit Mediastream asal tetapi ia sukar dinavigasi (old habit die hard). Oleh itu kulit ini menyelesaikan maasalah tersebut (Menu berada disebelah kiri)[CR] Semua penghargaan kepada Pasukan Razorfish atas konsep asal dan grafik yang diguna dalam versi ini</description>
    <description lang="nl">MediaStream Redux is een complete nieuw herontwerp vanaf het begin van Team Razorfish`s MediaStream ontwerp en gebruikt allen de originele ontwerpgraphics (ook zijn startscherm lay-out en sommige weergaven) en is alleen voor 16x9 en ondersteund geen 4x3 zoals het origineel [CR] Ik heb dit ontwerp gemaakt vanwege de Project mayhem ontwerpen die gemaakt zijn en die ik geweldig vond. Ik vond het erg lastig om om mijn manier te navigeren in het originele ontwerp. (oude liefde rust niet). daarom navigeerd dit ontwerp meer zoals de PM ontwerpen (Menu is aan de linker kant)[CR] alle credits gaan naar Team Razorfish voor het originele concept en graphics gebruikt in deze versie</description>
    <description lang="pt">   O tema MediaStream Redux é um completo reinventar do tema 'MediaStream', desenvolvido originalmente pela equipa Razorfish. Apenas usa alguns gráficos e organização de vistas do tema original, exclusivamente para ecrãs 16x9.[CR]   Desenvolvi este tema após o términos dos temas 'Project Mayhem'. Adorava o tema 'Mediastream' original mas achava muito difícil navegar nos menus (velhos hábitos fazem o monge). Assim, ao navegar, este tema comporta-se como os temas 'Project Mayhem' (Menus à esquerda).[CR]  Todos os créditos vão para a equipa 'Razorfish' pelo conceito original e gráficos usados nesta versão.</description>
    <description lang="ru">MediaStream Redux - это глубокая переделка обложки MediaStream от Team Razorfish, использующий оригинальную графику (а так же строение главного окна и некоторые другие формы), подходит только для 16x9, поддержки 4х3 нет.[CR] Я сделал эту обложку, потому что мне нравилось как выглядела оригинальная MediaStream от Team Razorfish, но она была очень сложна в управлении (от старых привычек сложно отделаться). Так что в плане управления данная обложка более близка к обложкам PM (с меню на левой стороне)[CR] Все благодарности уходят Team Razorfish за концепцию и графику, использованную в их версии.</description>
    <description lang="sv">MediaStream Redux är en från grunden omgjord version av Team Razorfish's MediaStream skal och använder bara originalets grafik (även layouten för hemmenyn och vissa av vyerna) och är enbart för 16x9, inget 4x3 stöd som originalet.[CR] Jag gjorde skalet för att jag älskade originalet, men då jag var van vid Project Mayhem-skalen fann jag det något svårnavigerat. Detta skal navigeras som i PM-skalen (menyn till vänster).[CR] Tack till Team Razorfish för originalkonceptet och grafiken som används i den här versionen.</description>
    <description lang="tr">MediaStream Redux Team Razorfish'in MediaStream görünümünün baştan aşağıya yeniden düzenlenmiş halidir. Orjinal grafikleri kullanır.(aynı zamanda ev penceresi ve bazı düzenler) Sadece 16x9 desteği vardır. 4x3 desteği yoktur.[CR] Bu görünümü Project Mayhem görünümünden geçmiş biri olarak orjinal Mediastrem görünümünü çok seviyordum fakat menüler çok karışık geliyordu. ( eskisi ölümdü resmen). Ben de bu görünümün dolaşımını PM kadar basit hale getirdim. (Menü sol tarafta)[CR] Bütün tebrikler Team Razorfish'e.  </description>
    <description lang="zh">MediaStream Redux是在Razorfish团队开发的MediaStream皮肤基础上完全重新编写的，仅使用了原皮肤的图形效果（它的主界面和一些视图），而且仅支持16x9显示而不是原皮肤的4x3。[CR]编写这个皮肤是因为相较于Project Mayhem皮肤，我更喜欢原Mediastream皮肤的效果，只是使用起来还有些不方便。现在这个皮肤的操作方式类似PM皮肤（菜单在左侧）[CR] 感谢来自于Razorfish团队的原始创意及相关图片资源</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
