<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="webinterface.awxi"
  version="0.6.5"
  name="AWXi"
  provider-name="MKay, Mizaki et al">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0"/>
    <import addon="xbmc.json" version="6.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.webinterface"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <summary lang="be">AWXi - Ajax based Webinterface for XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="bg">AWXi - уебинтерфейс базиран на Ajax за XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="cs">AWXi - Webové rozhraní Ajax pro XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="da">AWXi - Ajaxbaseret Webinterface til XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="de">AWXi - Ajax basiertes Webinterface fuer XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="el">AWXi - Διεπαφή Ιστού βασισμένη στο Ajax για το XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="en">AWXi - Ajax based Webinterface for XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="es">AWXi - Interfaz web basada en Ajax para XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">AWXi - Ajax-pohjainen webbikäyttöliittymä XBMC:lle</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">AWXi - Interface web de type Ajax pour XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="gl">AWXi - Interface Web para XBMC baseado en Ajax</summary>
  <summary lang="he">AWXi - Ajax based Webinterface for XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">AWXi - Ajax alapú webes kezelőfelület az XBMC-hez</summary>
  <summary lang="it">AWXi - Interfaccia Web basata su Ajax per XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="ko">AWXi - XBMC를 위한 Ajax 기반의 웹인터페이스</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">AWXi - Ajax interneto sąsaja į XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="nl">AWXi - Ajax gebaseerde Webinterface voor XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">AWXi - oparty na Ajaxie Interfejs WWW dla XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="pt">AWXi - Uma Webinterface para XBMC baseada em Ajax</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">AWXi -  Interface web baseada em Ajax para XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">AWXi - webové rozhranie pre XBMC založené na technológii Ajax</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">AWXi - Ajaxbaserat webbgränssnitt för XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="zh">AWXi - 基于Ajax的XBMC Web界面</summary>
  <description lang="be">You can use this webinterface to control the Audio/Video Section of XBMC: play/pause/stop/skip, show artists/albums/movies/tv shows and play them or add them to the playlist. It's designed for use on PCs or laptops with a browser like FireFox which supports JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Minimum requirements: XBMC Frodo &#10;Tested Browsers:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Not supported: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Hint: You may need to clear your browser-cache before you open the new installed/updated webinterface in your browser. It is highly recommended that you use a browser capable of using web sockets. IE 9 is not one of them.</description>
  <description lang="bg">Чрез уебинтерфейсът можете да: контролирате Музикалната и Видео секцията на XBMC - възпроизвеждане, пауза, стоп, пропускане; прегледате артистите, албумите, филмите и ТВ сериали, да ги възпроизведете или добавите към плейлист. Изграден е за ползване от компютри или лаптопи с браузър, като FireFox, който поддържа JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Минимални изисквания: XBMC Frodo &#10;Изпробвани браузъри:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Браузъри, които не се поддържат: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Съвет: Може да се наложи да изчистите кеша на браузъра преди да отворите нов прозорец на новоинсталиран/актуализиран уебинтерфейс. Препоръчително е ползването на браузър който поддържа web sockets. Internet Explorer 9 не поддържа.</description>
  <description lang="da">Du kan bruge dette webinterface til at styre Lyd/Video delen af XBMC: afspil/pause/stop/spol, vis kunstnere/albummer/film/tv-serier og afspil dem eller føj dem til afspilningslisten. Det er designet til brug på PC'er eller bærbare med en browser såsom Firefox som understøtter JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Minimumskrav: XBMC Frodo &#10;Testede Browsere:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Ikke understøttet: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Tip: Du skal muligvis rydde din browser-cache, før du åbner det installerede/opdaterede webinterface i din browser. Det anbefales at du anvender en browser, som kan håndtere web-sockets. IE 9 er ikke én af dem.</description>
  <description lang="de">Mit diesem Webinterface laesst sich die Audio- und Video-Sektion von XBMC steuern: play/pause/stop/skip, sowie Anzeigen/Abspielen von Interpreten/Alben/Filmen/Serien. Es wurde fuer den Einsatz an einem PC oder Laptop mit einem JavaScript-faehigen Browser wie FireFox entwickelt.&#10;&#10;Mindestvoraussetzung: XBMC Eden&#10;Getestete Browser:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Nicht unterstuetzt: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Hinweis: Sie muessen Ihren Browser-Cache leeren bevor Sie das neu installierte/aktualisierte Webinterface in Ihrem Browser laden.</description>
  <description lang="el">Μπορείτε να χρησιμοποιήσετε αυτή τη διεπαφή ιστού για να ελέγχετε το Τμήμα Βίντεο/Ήχου του XBMC: αναπαραγωγή/παύση/διακοπή/παράλειψη, προβολή καλλιτεχνών/άλμπουμ/ταινιών/τηλεοπτικών σειρών και αναπαραγωγή ή προσθήκη τους στη λίστα αναπαραγωγής. Είναι σχεδιασμένο για χρήση σε υπολογιστές με προγράμματα περιήγησης όπως το FireFox που υποστηρίζουν JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Ελάχιστες απαιτήσεις: XBMC Frodo&#10;Δοκιμασμένοι Περιηγητές:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Δεν υποστηρίζεται: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Υπόδειξη: Μπορεί να χρειαστεί να καθαρίσετε τον περιηγητή σας ή τη λανθάνουσα μνήμη προτού ανοίξετε τη νέα εγκατάσταση της διεπαφής ιστού στον περιηγητή σας. Προτείνεται ανεπιφύλακτα η χρήση ενός περιηγητή με δυνατότητα χρήσης web sockets. Ο IE 9 δεν είναι ένας από αυτούς.</description>
  <description lang="en">You can use this webinterface to control the Audio/Video Section of XBMC: play/pause/stop/skip, show artists/albums/movies/tv shows and play them or add them to the playlist. It's designed for use on PCs or laptops with a browser like FireFox which supports JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Minimum requirements: XBMC Frodo &#10;Tested Browsers:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Not supported: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Hint: You may need to clear your browser-cache before you open the new installed/updated webinterface in your browser. It is highly recommended that you use a browser capable of using web sockets. IE 9 is not one of them.</description>
  <description lang="es">Puedes usar esta interfaz web para controlar la sección de Audio/Vídeo de XBMC: reproducir/pausa/stop/omitir, mostrar artistas/álbumes/películas/series de TV y reproducirlas o agregarlas a la lista de reproducción. Está diseñado para ser usado en PCs o portátiles con un explorador como FireFox que soporte JavaScript.⏎ ⏎ Requisitos mínimos: XBMC Frodo ⏎ Exploradores probados:⏎ - FireFox⏎ - Chromium⏎ - Internet Explorer 9⏎ No soportados: Internet Explorer 6⏎ ⏎ Ayuda: Quizás necesites limpiar el cache de tu explorador antes de abrir tu nueva instalación/actualización de la interfaz web. Es altamente recomendable usar un explorador con capacidad de usar web sockets. IE 9 no es uno de ellos.</description>
  <description lang="fr">Cette interface web peut être utilisée pour contrôler tout ce qui concerne l'audio et la vidéo dans XBMC : Lecture / Pause / Arrêt / Suivant, affichage des artistes, albums, films et séries TV, avec la possibilité de les lire ou de les ajouter à la liste de lecture. Elle est conçue pour être utilisés sur un ordinateur fixe ou portable à l'aide d'un navigateur supportant le JavaScript comme Firefox.&#10;&#10;Prérequis minimaux : XMBC Frodo&#10;Navigateurs testés :&#10;- Firefox&#10;- Chromium&#10;- Internet Explorer 9&#10;Non supportés : Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Conseil : Il sera peut-être nécessaire de vider le cache du navigateur avant d'ouvrir l'interface nouvellement installée ou mise à jour. Il est fortement recommandé d'utiliser un navigateur qui utilise les Web Sockets. Internet Explorer 9 n'en fait pas partie.</description>
  <description lang="gl">Pode usar este interface web para controlar a Sección de Son/Vídeo do XBMC: reproducir/pausar/deter/saltar, amosar artistas/álbums/filmes/series e reproducilos ou engadilos a listaxe de reprodución. Deseñado para o seu uso nos PCs ou portátiles cun navegador coma FireFox que soporta JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Requirimentos mínimos: XBMC Frodo &#10;Navegadores Probados:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Sen soporte: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Suxestión: É posible que teña de limpar a caché do navegador antes de abrir a nova interface web. É moi recomendable usar un navegador que sexa compatible co uso de web sockets. IE 9 non é un deses.</description>
  <description lang="he">אתה יכול להשתמש בממשק אינטרנט זה על מנת לשלוט בפקדי האודיו/וידאו של XBMC: נגן/השהה/עצור/דלג,הצגת אומנים/אלבומים/סרטים/תוכניות טלויזיה ולנגן אותם או להוסיף אותם לרשימות ניגון.התוסף תוכנן לשימוש עם מחשב בעל דפדפן דוגמאות פיירפוקס או כרום שתומכים ב JavaScript.⏎⏎דרישות מינימום:XBMC frodo⏎נבדק על דפדפנים:⏎ - firefox⏎ - chromium⏎ -Internet explorer 9⏎אינו תומך ב:Internet explorer 6⏎⏎הערה:יכול להיות שתצטרף לנקות את מטמון הדפדפן שלך לפני שתפתח את התוסף.זה מומלץ מאוד להשתמש בדפדפן שמסוגל להשתמש בשקעי IE9 אינו אחד מהם.</description>
  <description lang="hu">Ezzel a webes kezelőfelülettel irányítani tudod az XBMC zene és videó lejátszását: indítás/megállítás/kihagyás, listák megjelenítése az előadókról/albumokról/filmekről/tv sorozatokról és ezek kiválasztása vagy lejátszási listához adása. Arra lett tervezve, hogy PC-n vagy mobil eszközön is használható legyen egy javascriptet támogató böngésző segítségével.⏎ ⏎Minimum követelmények: XBMC Frodo ⏎ Tesztelt böngészők: ⏎ - Firefox⏎ - Chromium⏎ - Internet Explorer 9⏎ Nem támogatott: Internet Explorer 6⏎ ⏎ Tipp: Lehet hogy a böngésző ideiglenes fájljait törölni kell, mielőtt az újonnan telepített webes felületet használod. Kifejezetten ajánlott, hogy websocket támogatott böngészőt használj. Az IE 9 nem ilyen.</description>
  <description lang="it">Puoi usare questa interfaccia web per controllare le sezioni Audio/Video di XBMC: play/pausa/stop/salta, mostra artisti/album/film/programmi tv, avviarli o aggiungerli alla playlist. E' disegnata per usare PC o laptop con un browser come FireFox che supporti JavaScript.⏎ ⏎ Requisiti Minimi: XBMC Frodo ⏎ Browser Testati:⏎ - FireFox⏎ - Chromium⏎ - Internet Explorer 9⏎ Non supportati: Internet Explorer 6⏎ ⏎ Consiglio: Può essere necessario pulire la cache del browser prima di aprire la nuova interfaccia web browser. E' altamente raccomandato l'utilizzo di un browser compatibile con i "web sockets". IE 9 non è uno di questi.</description>
  <description lang="ko">이 웹인터페이스로 XBMC의 오디오/비디오를 제어할 수 있습니다: 재생/일시정지/정지/건너뛰기, 아티스트/앨범/영화/TV쇼 보기와 재생 또는 재생목록에 추가. Java 스크립트를 지원하는 파이어폭스와 같은 브라우저로 PC나 노트북에서 사용하도록 개발되었습니다..&#10;&#10;최소 사양: XBMC Frodo &#10;지원하는 브라우저:&#10; - 파이어폭스&#10; - 크롬&#10; - 인터넷 익스플로러 9&#10;미지원: 인터넷 익스플로러 6&#10;&#10;힌트: 새로 설치하거나 업데이트한 웹인터페이스를 브라우저에서 열기 전에 브라우저 캐시를 지워야 할 수도 있습니다. web socket을 지원하는 브라우저 사용을 강력하게 권장합니다.  IE 9는 web socket을 지원하지 않습니다.</description>
  <description lang="nl">Je kunt deze webinterface gebruiken om de Audio/Video sectie van XBMC te besturen: afspelen/pauze/stop/overslaan, weergave artiest/albums/films/tv series en speel deze af of voeg deze toe aan een afspeellijst. Het is ontworpen voor gebruik op PC's of laptops met een browser als FireFox welke JavaScript ondersteund.&#10;&#10;Minimum eisen: XBMC Frodo &#10;Geteste Browsers:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Niet ondersteund: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Hint: Wellicht moet je de browser-cache leegmaken voordat je de nieuw geïnstalleerde of geupdate webinterface in je browser opent. Het is zeer aanbevolen dat je een browser gebruikt die sockets ondersteund. IE 9 behoort hier niet toe.</description>
  <description lang="pl">Ten Interfejs WWW pozwala kontrolować wybór, dodawanie do kolejki i proces odtwarzania zasobów audio / wideo, a wszystko to przy pomocy wygodnego interfejsu prezentującego zasoby multimedialne przy użyciu miniatur filmów, seriali tv, wykonawców i albumów muzycznych. AWXi został zaprojektowany do użytkowania na komputerach osobistych lub notebookach w przeglądarce obsługującej JavaScript, takiej jak FireFox.&#10;&#10;Minimalne wymagania: XBMC Eden &#10;Przetestowane przeglądarki internetowe:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chrome&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Nie obsługiwane: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Wskazówka: Po instalacji / aktualizacji, przed uruchomieniem AWX może być konieczne wyczyszczenie cache przeglądarki.</description>
  <description lang="pt">Pode usar esta webinterface para controlar as secções Áudio/Vídeo do XBMC: reproduzir/pausar/parar/próximo, exibir artistas/álbuns/filmes/séries tv e reproduzir ou adicionar à lista de reprodução. Está pronta para ser usada em PCs ou portáteis com um navegador como o Firefox que suporte JavaScript&#10;&#10;Requisitos mínimos: XBMC Frodo &#10;Navegadores Testados:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Não suportado: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Dica: Talvez precise de limpar a cache do seu navegador antes de abrir a webinterface recém-instalada ou actualizada. Sugerimos que utilize um navegador com capacidades de usar web sockets. O IE 9 não tem essa capacidade.</description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">Você pode usar esta interface web para controlar a seção de áudio/vídeo do XBMC: reproduzir/pausar/parar/pular, mostrar artistas/álbuns/filmes/séries de TV e reproduzi-los ou adicioná-los à lista de reprodução. É feita para ser usada em computadores com um navegador que suporta Javascript.&#10;&#10;Requisitos mínimos: XBMC Frodo &#10;Navegadores testados:&#10; - Firefox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Não suportado: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Dica: Você pode ter que limpar o cache do seu navegador antes de abrir a nova interface web instalada/atualizada. É altamente recomendado que você utilize um navegador com suporte a web sockets. O IE 9 não é um deles.</description>
  <description lang="sk">Toto webové rozhranie môžete použiť na ovládanie Audio/Video sekcií XBMC: prehrať/pozastaviť/zastaviť/preskočiť, zobraziť umelcov/albumy/filmy/seriály a prehrať ich či pridať do playlistu. Je navrhnutý pre PC alebo laptop s prehliadačom ako FireFox s podporou JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Minimálne požiadavky: XBMC Frodo&#10;Testované prehliadače:&#10; - Firefox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Nepodporované: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Tip: Môže byť potrebné vyčistiť medzi-pamäť prehliadača pred použitím nového/aktualizovaného webového rozhrania. Je odporúčané použiť prehliadač, ktorý je schopný pracovať s web-socketmi - IE9 medzi ne nepatrí. </description>
  <description lang="sv">Du kan använda detta webbgränsnitt för att kontrollera ljud/video-sektionen av XBMC: spela/pausa/stoppa/hoppa över, visa artister/album/filmer/tv-serier och spela dem eller lägga till dom i spellistan. Det är designat att användas på PC eller bärbara med en webbläsare likt FireFox som stödjer JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Minimum krav: XBMC Frodo&#10;Veriferade webbläsare:&#10;- FireFox&#10;- Chromium&#10;- Internet Explorer 9&#10;Inte stödda: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Tips: Du kan behöva rensa din webbläsarbuffert före du öppnar det nyinstallerade/uppdaterade webbgränssnittet i din läsare. Det är rekommenderat att du använder en läsare som kan använda webbsockets. IE 9 är inte en av dessa.</description>
  <description lang="zh">你可以使用此Web界面控制XBMC音/视频：播放/暂停/停止/跳过，显示艺术家/专辑/电影/剧集并播放或加入播放列表。用于台式机或便携机上支持JavaScript的浏览器，如FireFox。[CR][CR]最低要求：XBMC (pre) Eden[CR]测试浏览器：[CR] - FireFox[CR] - Chromium[CR] - Internet Explorer 9[CR]不支持：Internet Explorer 6[CR][CR]提示：当你在浏览器打开新安装或升级的Web界面前，可能需要先清除浏览器缓存。</description>
  <language>en cz</language>
  <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
