<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="webinterface.awxi"
  version="0.6.0"
  name="AWXi"
  provider-name="MKay, Mizaki et al">
  <requires>
  <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="3.00"/>
  <import addon="xbmc.json" version="4.00"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
  point="xbmc.gui.webinterface"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
  <summary lang="de">AWXi - Ajax basiertes Webinterface fuer XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="en">AWXi - Ajax based Webinterface for XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="es">AWXi - Interfaz web basada en Ajax para XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="fi">AWXi - Ajax-pohjainen webbikäyttöliittymä XBMC:lle</summary>
  <summary lang="fr">AWXi - Interface web de type Ajax pour XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="he">AWXi - Ajax based Webinterface for XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="hu">AWXi - Ajax alapú webes kezelőfelület az XBMC-hez</summary>
  <summary lang="it">AWXi - Interfaccia Web basata su Ajax per XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="lt">AWXi - Ajax interneto sąsaja į XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="pl">AWXi - oparty na Ajaxie Interfejs WWW dla XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="pt_BR">AWXi -  Webinterface baseado Ajax para XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="sk">AWXi - webové rozhranie pre XBMC založené na technológii Ajax</summary>
  <summary lang="sv">AWXi - Ajaxbaserat webbgränssnitt för XBMC</summary>
  <summary lang="zh">AWXi - 基于Ajax的XBMC Web界面</summary>
  <description lang="de">Mit diesem Webinterface laesst sich die Audio- und Video-Sektion von XBMC steuern: play/pause/stop/skip, sowie Anzeigen/Abspielen von Interpreten/Alben/Filmen/Serien. Es wurde fuer den Einsatz an einem PC oder Laptop mit einem JavaScript-faehigen Browser wie FireFox entwickelt.&#10;&#10;Mindestvoraussetzung: XBMC Eden&#10;Getestete Browser:&#10;   - FireFox&#10;   - Chromium&#10;   - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Nicht unterstuetzt: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Hinweis: Sie muessen Ihren Browser-Cache leeren bevor Sie das neu installierte/aktualisierte Webinterface in Ihrem Browser laden.</description>
  <description lang="en">You can use this webinterface to control the Audio/Video Section of XBMC: play/pause/stop/skip, show artists/albums/movies/tv shows and play them or add them to the playlist. It's designed for use on PCs or laptops with a browser like FireFox which supports JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Minimum requirements: XBMC Eden &#10;Tested Browsers:&#10;   - FireFox&#10;   - Chromium&#10;   - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Not supported: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Hint: You may need to clear your browser-cache before you open the new installed/updated webinterface in your browser.</description>
  <description lang="es">Puede usar esta interfaz web para controlar la sección de Audio/Video de XBMC: reproducir/pausar/parar/saltar, mostrar artistas/álbumes/películas/programas de TV y reproducirlos o añadirlos a la lista de reproducción. Está diseñada para ser usada en PCs o portátiles con un navegador similar a FireFox con soporte para JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Requerimientos mínimos: XBMC Eden&#10;Navegadores compatibles:&#10;- FireFox&#10;- Chrome&#10;- Internet Explorer 9&#10;No compatibles: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Consejo: Probablemente deba limpiar la caché del navegador antes de abrir la interfaz web que ha instalado/actualizado en su navegador.</description>
  <description lang="fr">Vous pouvez utiliser cette interface web pour contrôler la section audio/vidéo de XBMC: jouer/pause/arrêter/sauter, afficher les artistes/albums/films/séries tv et les jouer ou les ajouter à la liste d'écoute. Il est conçu pour être utilisé sur un PC ou un ordinateur portable avec un navigateur web comme Firefox qui supporte JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Exigences minimales: XBMC Eden &#10;Navigateurs compatibles:&#10;   - FireFox&#10;   - Chromium&#10;   - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Non compatibles: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Indice: Il sera peut-être nécessaire d'effacer la mémoire cache de votre navigateur avant d'ouvrir la nouvelle installation/mise à jour de l'interface web dans votre navigateur.</description>
  <description lang="he">You can use this webinterface to control the Audio/Video Section of XBMC: play/pause/stop/skip, show artists/albums/movies/tv shows and play them or add them to the playlist. It's designed for use on PCs or laptops with a browser like FireFox which supports JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Minimum requirements: XBMC Eden &#10;Tested Browsers:&#10;   - FireFox&#10;   - Chromium&#10;   - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Not supported: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Hint: You may need to clear your browser-cache before you open the new installed/updated webinterface in your browser.</description>
  <description lang="it">Puoi usare questa interfaccia web per contorllare le sezioni Audio/Video di XBMC: play, pausa, stop, salta, mostra artisti/album/film/tv e riprodurli o aggiungerli alla playlist. È progettata per essere usata con un PC o portatile con un browser tipo FireFox con supporto JavaScript. &#10;&#10;Requisiti minimi: XBMC Eden &#10; Browser testati:&#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10; Non supportati: Internet Explorer 6 &#10; Suggerimento: Potrebbe essere necessario svuotare la cache del browser prima di aprire l'interfaccia web appena intallata/aggiornata nel tuo browser.</description>
  <description lang="lt">Jūs galite naudoti šią tinklapio sąsają, norėdami kontroliuoti Audio/Video skirsnį XBMC: Groti/Pauzė/Stabdyti/Praleisti, rodyti Artistai/Albumai/Filmai/TV laidas ir paleisti juos arba įtraukti juos į grojaraštį. Jis skirtas naudoti HTPC media centruose ar kitame  kompiuteryje, Firefox naršykle, kuri palaiko JavaScript.&#10; Minimalūs reikalavimai: XBMC Eden ir aukščiau &#10; Išbandytos naršyklės: &#10; - FireFox&#10; - Chromium&#10; - Internet Explorer 9&#10; Nepalaikoma: Internet Explorer 6 &#10; Užuomina/Patarimas: Jums gali prireikti išvalyti savo naršyklės talpyklą, prieš atidarydami naują įdiegtą/atnaujintą interneto sąsają savo naršyklėje.</description>
  <description lang="pl">Ten Interfejs WWW pozwala kontrolować wybór, dodawanie do kolejki i proces odtwarzania zasobów audio / wideo, a wszystko to przy pomocy wygodnego interfejsu prezentującego zasoby multimedialne przy użyciu miniatur filmów, seriali tv, wykonawców i albumów muzycznych. AWXi został zaprojektowany do użytkowania na komputerach osobistych lub notebookach w przeglądarce obsługującej JavaScript, takiej jak FireFox.&#10;&#10;Minimalne wymagania: XBMC Eden &#10;Przetestowane przeglądarki internetowe:&#10;   - FireFox&#10;   - Chrome&#10;   - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Nie obsługiwane: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Wskazówka: Po instalacji / aktualizacji, przed uruchomieniem AWX może być konieczne wyczyszczenie cache przeglądarki.</description>
  <description lang="pt_BR">Você pode usar esta webinterface para controlar a seção de Áudio/Vídeo do XBMC: play/pausa/parar/pular, mostrar artistas/álbuns/filmes/seriados e reproduzi-los ou ainda adicionar a uma playlist. Foi desenhada para uso em PCs ou laptops com um navegador como Firefox com suporte JavaScript. ⏎ ⏎ Requerimentos Mínimos: XBMC Eden ⏎ Navegadores testados:⏎   - FireFox⏎   - Chromium⏎   - Internet Explorer 9⏎ Não suportado: Internet Explorer 6⏎ ⏎ Dica: Você deve limpar o cache de seu navegador antes de abrir, instalar ou atualizar webinterface em seu navegador.</description>
  <description lang="sk">Toto webové rozhranie je možné použiť na ovládanie audio/video sekcie XBMC: spustiť prehrávanie/pozastaviť prehrávanie/zastaviť prehrávanie/preskočiť položku, zobraziť umelcov/albumy/filmy/tv relácie a prehrávať alebo pridať ich do zoznamu skladieb/videí. Bolo navrhnuté pre použitie na PC alebo notebookoch s prehliadačom ako FireFox, ktorý podporuje JavaScript.&#10;&#10;Minimálne požiadavky: XBMC Eden &#10;Testované prehliadače:&#10;   - FireFox&#10;   - Chromium&#10;   - Internet Explorer 9&#10;Nepodporované: Internet Explorer 6&#10;&#10;Tip: Skôr, než otvoríte novo nainštalované/aktualizované webové rozhranie vo vašom prehliadači, možno bude potrebné vymazať cache zásobník prehliadača.</description>
  <description lang="sv">Du kan använda detta webbgränssnitt för att kontrollera musik/video-sektionen av XBMC: spela/pausa/stoppa/skippa, visa artister/album/filmer/tv-serier och spela den eller lägga till dom i spellista. Det är designat för att använda på PC och bärbara med en webbläsare liknande FireFox som stödjer JavaScript.⏎ ⏎ Minimikrav: XBMC Eden⏎Testade webbläsare:⏎ - FireFox⏎ - Chromium⏎ - Internet Explorer 9⏎ Inte stödda: Internet Explorer 6⏎ ⏎ Tips: Du kan behöva rensa din webbläsar-buffert innan du kan öppna nyligen installerade/uppdaterade webbgränssnitt i din webbläsare.</description>
  <description lang="zh">你可以使用此Web界面控制XBMC音/视频：播放/暂停/停止/跳过，显示艺术家/专辑/电影/剧集并播放或加入播放列表。用于台式机或便携机上支持JavaScript的浏览器，如FireFox。[CR][CR]最低要求：XBMC (pre) Eden[CR]测试浏览器：[CR]   - FireFox[CR]   - Chromium[CR]   - Internet Explorer 9[CR]不支持：Internet Explorer 6[CR][CR]提示：当你在浏览器打开新安装或升级的Web界面前，可能需要先清除浏览器缓存。</description>
  <language>en de fr ru pl cn</language>
  </extension>
</addon>

