<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.service.checkpreviousepisode" name="XBMC Check Previous Episode" version="0.3.1" provider-name="Lucleonhart">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
	<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="default.py" start="login"></extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">Проверяване състоянието на предходния епизод</summary>
    <summary lang="de">XBMC überrüfen des vorherigen Epsiodenstatus</summary>
    <summary lang="en">XBMC check previous episode state</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">XBMC vérifier l'état de l'épisode précédent</summary>
    <summary lang="it">XBMC verifica lo stato dell'episodio precedente</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">XBMC controleer de staat van de vorige aflevering</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Sprawdzanie stanu obejrzanych odcinków seriali</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Verificar o estado do episódio anterior no XBMC</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Когато пускате епизод от даден сериал скриптът проверява предхождащия и предупреждава ако той отсъства от библиотеката или не е изгледан.</description>
    <description lang="de">Dieses Script überprüft die vorige Episode der TV Show die gerade gestartet werden soll und warnt falls diese noch nicht gesehen wurde oder nicht vorhanden ist!</description>
    <description lang="en">This scripts checks the previous episode from the one you started to watch and warns you if it is missing from your library or unwatched!</description>
    <description lang="fr">Ce script vérifie le précédent épisode de celui que vous lancer pour regarder et vous avertit s'il est absent de votre médiathèque ou non vu !</description>
    <description lang="it">Questo script verifica l'episodio precedente rispetto a quello che hai iniziato a guardare e ti avvisa se questo manca nella tua libreria, o se manca !</description>
    <description lang="nl">Dit script controleert de vorige aflevering vanaf de aflevering die je begon te kijken en waarschuwt u als de aflevering mist in de bibliotheek of als u die aflevering nog niet hebt gezien!</description>
    <description lang="pl">Niniejszy skrypt sprawdza stan obejrzanych odcinków seriali i informuje użytkownika, jeśli występują braki w bibliotece lub są jakieś nieobejrzane odcinki!</description>
    <description lang="pt">Este script verifica o episódio anterior ao episódio que está a ver, e avisa se está em falta na sua biblioteca ou se está por ver.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <language></language>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=151531</forum>
    <website>http://www.lucleonhart.de</website>
    <source>git://github.com/Lucleonhart/script.service.checkpreviousepisode.git</source>
    <email>xbmc at lucleonhart dot de</email>
  </extension>
</addon>
