<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.service.checkpreviousepisode" name="XBMC Check Previous Episode" version="0.3.2" provider-name="Lucleonhart">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
	<import addon="xbmc.addon" version="12.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="default.py" start="login"></extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Kodi check vorige episode toestand</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Проверява състоянието на предходния епизод</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Kodi comprovar estat del episodi anterior</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Kodi kontroluje stav předchozí epizody</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Vorherigen Folgenstatus von Kodi überprüfen</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Έλεγχος προηγούμενου επεισοδίου από το Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Kodi check previous episode state</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Kodi check previous episode state</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Kodi checks previous episode state</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Kodi comprobar estado del episodio anterior</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Kodi tarkistaa aiemman jakson tilan</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Kodi vérifier l'état de l'épisode précédent</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Kodi vérifie l'état de l'épisode précédent</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Verificar o estado do episodio anterior no Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="he">Kodi בודק מצב פרק קודם</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Kodi provjerava status prijašnje epizode</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Kodi ellenőrzi az előző epizód állapotát</summary>
    <summary lang="id">Kodi memeriksa kondisi episode sebelumnya</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Kodi athugun á stöðu fyrri þáttaraðar</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Kodi verifica lo stato dell'episodio precedente</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">이전 회차 에피소드 상태를 확인합니다</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Kodi patikrina ankstesnio epizodo būseną</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Kodi controleer de staat van de vorige aflevering</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Kodi sjekk forrige episodes tilstand</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Sprawdzanie stanu obejrzanych odcinków seriali</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Verificar o estado do episódio anterior no Kodi</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Kodi verifica o estado do episódio anterior</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Kodi проверяет состояние предыдущей серии</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Kodi zistenie stavu predchádzajúcej epizódy</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Kodi kontrollera föregående avsnittsstatus</summary>
    <description lang="af">Hierdie skripte gaan die vorige episodes na van die een wat jy begin kyk het en waarsku jou as dit is weg uit jou biblioteek of laat staan is​​!</description>
    <description lang="bg">Когато пускате епизод от даден сериал скриптът проверява предходния и предупреждава ако той отсъства от библиотеката или не е изгледан.</description>
    <description lang="ca">Aquest script comprova el episodi anterior que has començat a veure i t'avisa si no està en la teva llibreria o no l'has vist!</description>
    <description lang="cs">Tento skript kontroluje předchozí epizody od té, kterou jste začaly sledovat a upozorní vás, pokud chybí ve vaší knihovny nebo je nezhlédnutá!</description>
    <description lang="de">Dieses Skript überprüft die vorige Folge der Sendung die gerade gestartet werden soll und warnt falls diese noch nicht gesehen wurde oder nicht vorhanden ist!</description>
    <description lang="el">Αυτό το πρόγραμμα ελέγχει το προηγούμενο επεισόδιο από αυτό που ξεκινήσατε να βλέπετε, και σας προειδοποιεί αν λείπει από τη συλλογή σας, ή αν υπάρχει αλλά δεν το έχετε δει.</description>
    <description lang="en">This scripts checks the previous episode from the one you started to watch and warns you if it is missing from your library or unwatched!</description>
    <description lang="en_US">This script checks the previous episode from the one you started to watch and warns you if it is missing from your library or unwatched!</description>
    <description lang="es">Este script comprueba el episodio anterior al que vas a empezar a ver y te avisa si el anterior no está en tu colección o si aún no lo has visto.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Tämä skripti tarkistaa aiemman jakson tilan ja ilmoittaa jos se puuttuu sinulta tai et ole katsonut sitä!</description>
    <description lang="fr">Ce script vérifie que l'existence de l'épisode précédent celui que vous regardez et vous avertit s'il est absent de votre médiathèque ou non vu !</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Ce script vérifie l'épisode précédent celui que vous avez commencé à regarder et vous avertit s'il est absent de votre vidéothèque ou s'il n'a pas été regardé!</description>
    <description lang="gl">Este script verifica o episodio anterior ao que está a ver, e avísalle de se non está na súa biblioteca ou se aínda non o viu!</description>
    <description lang="he">סקריפט זה בודק את הפרק הקודם מזה שהתחלת לצפות בו כעת ומתריע אם הוא חסר מהספריה שלך או שלא צפית בו.</description>
    <description lang="hr">Ova skripta provjerava epizodu prije one koju ste počeli gledati i upozorava vas ako nedostaje u vašoj videoteci ili je nepogledana!</description>
    <description lang="hu">Ez a szkript ellenőrzi hogy az előző epizód megtekintésre került-e és értesít hogyha hiányzik a médiatárból, vagy megnézetlen állapotban van!</description>
    <description lang="is">Þessi skrifta athugar stöðu á næstu þáttaröð á undan þeirri sem þú byrjaðir að horfa á og varar þig við að hana vanti eða þú sért ekki búinn að sjá hana!</description>
    <description lang="it">Questo script verifica l'episodio precedente rispetto a quello che hai iniziato a guardare e ti avvisa se questo manca nella tua libreria, o se manca !</description>
    <description lang="ko">이 스크립트는 감상을 시작한 TV쇼의 이전 에피소드를 확인해서 라이브러리에 없거나 감상하지 않은 에피소드가 있으면 알려줍니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Šis skriptas patikrina ankstesnį epizodą pagal tą, kurį pradėjote žiūrėti ir įspėja jus, jei jo trūksta jūsų bibliotekoje arba jis neperžiūrėtas!</description>
    <description lang="nl">Dit script controleert de vorige aflevering vanaf de aflevering die je begon te kijken en waarschuwt je als de aflevering mist in de bibliotheek of als je die aflevering nog niet hebt gezien!</description>
    <description lang="no">Dette skriptet sjekker episoden før den du starter og gir deg melding om den er sett eller mangler fra biblioteket ditt.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Niniejszy skrypt sprawdza stan obejrzanych odcinków seriali i informuje użytkownika, jeśli występują braki w bibliotece lub są jakieś nieobejrzane odcinki!</description>
    <description lang="pt">Este script verifica o episódio anterior ao episódio que está a ver, e avisa se está em falta na sua biblioteca ou se está por ver.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este script verifica o estado do episódio anterior do seriado que você está acompanhando e lhe avisa se estiver ausente em sua coleção ou que o mesmo ainda não foi assistido.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Данный скрипт проверяет предыдущую серию по отношению к той, которую вы начали смотреть, и оповещает если её нет в вашей библиотеки или она не была просмотрена!</description>
    <description lang="sk">Tento skript skontroluje stav predchádzajúcej epizódy od tej, ktorú ste práve spustili, a upozorní vás v prípade, že táto epizóda chýba vo vašej knižnici alebo je označená ako nevidená!</description>
    <description lang="sv">Detta script kontrollerar det föregående avsnittet från det avsnitt du började titta på och låter dig veta om det saknas i ditt bibliotek eller om du inte tittat på det än.</description>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=151531</forum>
    <website>http://www.lucleonhart.de</website>
    <email>xbmc at lucleonhart dot de</email>
    <source>git://github.com/Lucleonhart/script.service.checkpreviousepisode.git</source>
  </extension>
</addon>
