<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.confluence.modified"
  version="2.1.1"
  name="Confluence Modified"
  provider-name="Jezz_X, Team XBMC, SpaceMonkey">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.0.0"/>
    <import addon="service.library.data.provider" version="0.0.1"/>
    <import addon="script.favourites" version="4.0.9"/>
    <import addon="script.randomandlastitems" version="2.1.6"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt"
    debugging="true"
    effectslowdown="0.75">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">Confluence oortreksel deur Jezz_X, modifikasies deur SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Pell Confluence per Jezz_X, modificacions per SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Confluence Skin von Jezz_X, Anpassungen von SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Το κέλυφος Confluence από τον Jezz_X, με μετατροπές από τον SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Confluence skin by Jezz_X, modifications by SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Confluence skin by Jezz_X, modifications by SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Confluence skin by Jezz_X, modifications by SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Confluence skin by Jezz_X, modifications by SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Skin Confluence de Jezz_X, modificaciones de SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Confluence rüü autorilt Jezz_X, muudatused ja täiendusex on teinud SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Habillage Confluence par Jezz_X, modifications par SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="he">המעטפת Confluence של Jezz_X, שינויים ע"י SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Confluence Felszín Jezz_X-től, módoítva SpaceMonkey által.</summary>
    <summary lang="is">Confluence viðmót eftir Jezz_X, breytt af SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Skin Confluence di Jazz_X, modifiche a cura di SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Confluence 스킨 Jezz_X 만듦,  SpaceMonkey 수정</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Confluence teminė išvaizda, kurią sukūrė Jezz_X bei modifikavo SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Kulit Confluence oleh Jezz_X, pengubahsuaian oleh SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Confluence skin door Jezz_X, Modificaties door SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Zmodyfikowana przez SpaceMonkey wersja skóry Confluence autorstwa Jezz_X</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Tema Confluence por Jezz_X, e modificado por SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Skin Confluence por Jezz_X, modificações por SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Обложка Confluence от Jezz_X, модификации от SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Confluence skal av Jezz_X, modifieringar av SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">基于Jezz_X开发的Confluence皮肤，SpaceMonkey的修改版本</summary>
    <description lang="af">Confluence is die bestek oortreksel vir Kodi 9.11 en op. Dit is 'n kombinasie van konsepte van 'n klomp gewilde oortreksels, en probeer om hulle goeie idees te omhels en integreer in 'n oortreksel wat maklik behoort te wees om te verstaan en gebruik vir eerste keer Kodi gebruikers. Hierdie is 'n veranderde weergawe van Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="de">Confluence ist der Standard-Skin für Kodi 9.11 und höher. Er ist eine Kombination von Ideen aus vielen populären Skins und versucht deren beste Eigenschaften in einem Skin zu vereinen, der für Kodi-Neulinge einfach zu verstehen und zu nutzen ist. Es ist eine angepasste Version von Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="el">Το Confluence είναι το προεπιλεγμένο κέλυφος για τις εκδόσεις Kodi 9.11 και άνω. Είναι ένας συνδυασμός από πολλά δημοφιλή κελύφη, και επιχειρεί να συμπεριλάβει τις καλύτερες ιδέες τους σε ένα κέλυφος το οποίο είναι εύκολο σε αρχάριους χρήστες του Kodi να κατανοήσουν και χρησιμοποιήσουν. Αυτή είναι μια τροποποιημένη έκδοση του Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="en">Confluence is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use. This is a modified version of Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Confluence is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use. This is a modified version of Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Confluence is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use. This is a modified version of Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Confluence is the default skin for Kodi 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time Kodi users to understand and use. This is a modified version of Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Confluence es el skin por defecto para Kodi 9.11 y siguientes. Es una combinación de conceptos de varios skins populares, e intenta integrar buenas ideas en un skin que haga fácil en entendimiento y el uso a los usuarios que inician en Kodi.</description>
    <description lang="et">Confluence on vaikerüü Kodi-le alates versioonist 9.11. Confluence on paljude populaarsete rüüde kombineerimise tulemus, mis üritab omavahel tööle panna teiste rüüde parimaid lahendusi, et saavutada rüü, mis oleks esmakasutajale ühtmoodi selge ja kerge kasutada. Tegemist on Confluence'i muudetud ja täiustatud versiooniga.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Confluence est le thème par défaut de Kodi 9.11 et ultérieur. Il se base sur les concepts présents dans de nombreux thèmes populaires, et tente d'intégrer leurs bonnes idées dans un même thème qui devrait être facile d'utilisation. Il s'agit d'une version modifiée de Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Confluence est l'habillage par défaut pour Kodi 9.11 et ultérieure. C'est une combinaison de concepts provenant de plusieurs habillages populaires, qui tente d'intégrer leurs bonnes idées en un habillage qui devrait être facile à comprendre et à utiliser pour les utilisateurs novices de Kodi. Ceci est la version modifiée de Confluence. </description>
    <description lang="he">המעטפת Confluence היא מעטפת ברירת המחדל של Kodi. המעטפת הינה תוצר של אימוץ מאפיינים ממעטפות פופולריות רבות תוך רצון לשלב מאפיינים אלה למעטפת פשוטה לשימוש ולהכרה ראשונית ע"י משתמשי Kodi חדשים.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Confluence az alapértelmezett felszín az Kodi 9.11 és afölött. Ez több népszerű felszín koncepcióját fogja össze, és megkísérli ötvözni a jó ötleteket azzal a céllal hogy könnyen érthetővé és használhatóvá váljon a kezdő Kodi felhasználók számára is. Ez egy módisított változata a Confluence felszínnek.</description>
    <description lang="is">Confluence er sjálfgefið viðmót fyrir Kodi 9.11 og nýrra. Það er samansafn af hugmyndum frá mörgum vinsælum viðmótum, og reynir að meðtaka og sameina góðar hugmyndir í viðmóti sem er auðvelt fyrir nýja Kodi notendur að skilja og nota. Þetta er breytt útgáfa af Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="it">La Confluence è la skin di default per le versioni di Kodi a partire dalla 9.11. E' una combinazione delle skin più popolari e cerca di integrare le migliori idee in una skin che risulti facile da comprendere ed utilizzare per i nuovi utenti di Kodi. Questa è una versione modificata della Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="ko">Confluence 는 Kodi 9.11 이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 많은 인기 스킨의 컨셉과 좋은 아이디어를 모아서 하나의 스킨으로 만들었으며 초보자도 사용하기 쉽습니다. 이 버전은 Confluence를 수정한 버전입니다.</description>
    <description lang="lt">Confluence yra numatytoji teminė išvaizda pradedant Kodi 9.11 versija. Tai daugelio populiarių teminų išvaizdų derinys, mėginantis perimti ir integruoti jų geriausias idėjas į teminę išvaizdą, kuri turėtų būti lengvai suprantama ir naudojama varotojų, pirmą kartą naudojančių Kodi. Tai yra modifikuota Confluence versija.</description>
    <description lang="ms">Confluence adalah kulit lalai untuk Kodi 9.11 dan ke atas. Ia adalah gabungan konsep dari banyak jenis kulit yang terkenal, dan percubaan untuk menyepadukan idea mereka ke dalam kulit yang sepatutnya mudah bagi pengguna Kodi buat kali pertama memahaminya dan seterusnya menggunakannya. Ia merupakan versi Confluence yang telah diubahsuai.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Confluence is de standaard skin voor Kodi 9.11 en hoger. Het is een combinatie van concepten van vele andere populaire skins. Het tracht hun goede ideeën te integreren in een skin die gemakkelijk in gebruik is voor gebruikers die voor het eerst Kodi gebruiken, dit zodat ze het gaan berijpen en gebruiken. Dit is een gemodificeerde versie van Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Confluence jest domyślną skóra dla Kodi w wersji 9.11 lub nowszych. Jest kombinacją pomysłów z wielu popularnych skór i próba zawarcia tego, co w nich najlepsze w skórze, która będzie łatwa do opanowania dla początkującego użytkownika. To jest zmodyfikowana wersja skóry Confulence.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Confluence é o tema predefinido para o Kodi 9.11 e versões superiores. este é uma combinação de conceitos de muitos temas populares, e integra as boas ideias num tema que deveria ser fácil para quem utiliza o Kodi pela primeira vez, para o compreenderem e utlizá-lo. Esta é uma versão modificada do Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Confluence é a skin padrão do Kodi 9.11 e superior. É uma combinação de conceitos de muitas skins populares e tenta integrar suas boas ideias. Deve ser fácil para usuários novatos do Kodi entender e utilizar. Esta é uma versão modifcada de Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Confluence - это стандартная обложка для Kodi 9.11 и выше. Представляет собой комбинацию концепций различных популярных обложек, сочетающая в себе их лучшие идеи в попытке предоставить наиболее простой и понятный интерфейс для тех, кто впервые использует Kodi. Данная версия является модификацией Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Confluence är standardskalet för Kodi 9.11 och högre. Det är en kombination av koncept från flera populära skal och försöker omfamna och integrera deras goda idéer till ett skal som skall vara enkelt för förstagångsanvändare att använda och förstå. Detta är en modifierad version av Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="zh">Confluence 是 Kodi 9.11 及以上版本的默认皮肤. 它整合来了很多流行皮肤的理念, 并尝试吸收和整合它们好的创意, 形成一个让初次使用Kodi的用户容易理解和使用的皮肤.  这是一个Confluence皮肤的修改版本.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
