<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon
  id="skin.confluence.modified"
  version="1.1.8"
  name="Confluence Modified"
  provider-name="Jezz_X, Team XBMC, SpaceMonkey">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="12.0.21"/>
    <import addon="script.favourites" version="4.0.9"/>
    <import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.27"/>
    <import addon="script.randomandlastitems" version="2.1.6"/>
    <import addon="script.videolanguage" version="0.1.0"/>
    <import addon="script.grab.fanart" version="0.12.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension
    point="xbmc.gui.skin"
    defaultthemename="textures.xbt"
    debugging="true"
    effectslowdown="0.75">
    <res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="ca">Pell Confluence per Jezz_X, modificacions per SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Confluence skin by Jezz_X, modifications by SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Confluence Felszín Jezz_X-től, módoítva SpaceMonkey által.</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Confluence 스킨 Jezz_X 만듦,  SpaceMonkey 수정</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Kulit Confluence oleh Jezz_X, pengubahsuaian oleh SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Confluence skin door Jezz_X, Modificaties door SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">O tema Confluence é da autoria de Jezz_X, com modificações feitas por SpaceMonkey</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">基于Jezz_X开发的Confluence皮肤，SpaceMonkey的修改版本</summary>
    <description lang="en">Confluence is the default skin for XBMC 9.11 and above. It is a combination of concepts from many popular skins, and attempts to embrace and integrate their good ideas into a skin that should be easy for first time XBMC users to understand and use. This is a modified version of Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Confluence az alapértelmezett felszín az XBMC 9.11 és afölött. Ez több népszerű felszín koncepcióját fogja össze, és megkísérli ötvözni a jó ötleteket azzal a céllal hogy könnyen érthetővé és használhatóvá váljon a kezdő XBMC felhasználók számára is. Ez egy módisított változata a Confluence felszínnek.</description>
    <description lang="ko">Confluence 는 XBMC 9.11 이상의 기본 스킨입니다. 많은 인기 스킨의 컨셉과 좋은 아이디어를 모아서 하나의 스킨으로 만들었으며 초보자도 사용하기 쉽습니다. 이 버전은 Confluence를 수정한 버전입니다.</description>
    <description lang="ms">Confluence adalah kulit lalai untuk XBMC 9.11 dan ke atas. Ia adalah gabungan konsep dari banyak jenis kulit yang terkenal, dan percubaan untuk menyepadukan idea mereka ke dalam kulit yang sepatutnya mudah bagi pengguna XBMC buat kali pertama memahaminya dan seterusnya menggunakannya. Ia merupakan versi Confluence yang telah diubahsuai.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Confluence is de standaard skin voor XBMC 9.11 en hoger. Het is een combinatie van concepten van vele andere populaire skins. Het tracht hun goede ideeën te integreren in een skin die gemakkelijk in gebruik is voor gebruikers die voor het eerst XBMC gebruiken, dit zodat ze het gaan berijpen en gebruiken. Dit is een gemodificeerde versie van Confluence.</description>
    <description lang="zh">Confluence 是 XBMC 9.11 及以上版本的默认皮肤. 它整合来了很多流行皮肤的理念, 并尝试吸收和整合它们好的创意, 形成一个让初次使用XBMC的用户容易理解和使用的皮肤.  这是一个Confluence皮肤的修改版本.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
