<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.openelec.settings"
       name="@DISTRONAME@ Configuration"
       version="@ADDONVERSION@"
       provider-name="OpenELEC">
   <requires>
   	<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="default.py"></extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service"       library="service.py" start="startup"></extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="af">@DISTRONAME@ Konfigurasie</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Настройки на @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Configuració de @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">@DISTRONAME@ Nastavení</summary>
    <summary lang="da">@DISTRONAME@ konfiguration</summary>
    <summary lang="de">@DISTRONAME@-Konfiguration</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Διαμόρφωση του @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="en">@DISTRONAME@ Configuration</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">@DISTRONAME@ Configuration</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">@DISTRONAME@ Configuration</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">@DISTRONAME@ Configuration</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Configuración de @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Configuración de @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="et">@DISTRONAME@ Seadistus</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">@DISTRONAME@-asetukset</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Configuration @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Configuration d'@DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Configuración do @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="he">הגדרות @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">@DISTRONAME@ podešavanje</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">@DISTRONAME@ konfiguráció</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Impostazioni @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">@DISTRONAME@設定</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">@DISTRONAME@ 설정</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">@DISTRONAME@ konfigūravimas</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">@DISTRONAME@ Configuratie</summary>
    <summary lang="no">@DISTRONAME@-konfigurasjon</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Konfiguracja @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Configuração @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Configuração do @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Configurare @DISTRONAME@ </summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Конфигурация @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Konfigurácia @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Prilagoditev @DISTRONAME@</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">@DISTRONAME@-konfiguration</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">@DISTRONAME@ Yapılandırması</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">@DISTRONAME@ Cấu hình</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">@DISTRONAME@ 设置</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Ползвайте добавката за да управлявате операционната система, в основата на @DISTRONAME@. Чрез добавката можете да настроите всичко и така не се налага да се притеснявате какво работи под Kodi.[CR][CR]От добавката можете да променяте настройките на мрежовите връзки, клавиатурната подредба и да включвате/изключвате отдалечения достъп посредством Samba или SSH.</description>
    <description lang="ca">Utilitza aquest complement per configurar el sistema operatiu subjacent del sistema @DISTRONAME@. Des d'aquí es pot gestionar tot el sistema, de manera que no s'ha de preocupar sobre el que s'executa sota el Kodi.[CR][CR]Des d'aquí es pot canviar la connectivitat de la xarxa, la distribució del teclat i idioma i activar / desactivar l'accés remot inclòs samba i SSH.</description>
    <description lang="cs">Použijte toto rozšíření pro správu vašeho @DISTRONAME@ systému. Odtud můžete spravovat celý systém, takže nemusíte mít strach o to, co běží pod kapotou. [CR] [CR] Odtud můžete změnit připojení k síti, rozložení klávesnice, jazyk a povolit nebo zakázat vzdálený přístup, včetně Samby a SSH.</description>
    <description lang="da">Brug denne addon til at styre dit @DISTRONAME@ systems underliggende operativsystem. Herfra kan du styre hele systemet, så du ikke behøver at bekymre dig om, hvad der kører under motorhjelmen. [CR] [CR] Herfra kan du ændre din netværksforbindelse, dit tastaturlayout og sprog og aktivere/deaktivere fjernadgang, herunder Samba og SSH.</description>
    <description lang="de">Verwenden Sie dieses Addon, um das Betriebssystem, auf dem @DISTRONAME@ läuft, zu administrieren. Von hier aus können Sie das gesamte System verwalten ohne sich Gedanken machen zu müssen, was genau im System abläuft.[CR][CR]Hier haben Sie die Möglichkeit Netzwerkeinstellungen, Tastaturlayouts oder Systemdienste, wie SSH oder Samba, zu konfigurieren.</description>
    <description lang="el">Χρησιμοποιήστε αυτό το πρόσθετο για να διαχειριστείτε το λειτουργικό σύστημα @DISTRONAME@. Από εδώ μπορείτε να διαχειριστείτε ολόκληρο το σύστημα ούτως ώστε να μη χρειάζεται να ανησυχείτε σχετικά με το τι τρέχει στο υπόβαθρο.[CR][CR]Μπορείτε, επίσης, να αλλάξετε τη συνδεσιμότητα του δικτύου σας, τη διάταξη του πληκτρολογίου σας και τη γλώσσα, καθώς και να ενεργοποιήσετε/απενεργοποιήσετε την απομακρυσμένη πρόσβαση μέσω Samba και SSH.</description>
    <description lang="en">Use this addon to manage your @DISTRONAME@ system's underlying operating system. From here you can manage the entire system so you don't have to worry about what runs under the hood.[CR][CR]From here you can change your network connectivity, your keyboard layout and language and enable/disable remote access including Samba and SSH.</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Use this addon to manage your @DISTRONAME@ system's underlying operating system. From here you can manage the entire system so you don't have to worry about what runs under the hood.[CR][CR]From here you can change your network connectivity, your keyboard layout and language and enable/disable remote access including Samba and SSH.</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Use this addon to manage your @DISTRONAME@ system's underlying operating system. From here you can manage the entire system so you don't have to worry about what runs under the hood.[CR][CR]From here you can change your network connectivity, your keyboard layout and language and enable/disable remote access including Samba and SSH.</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Use this addon to manage your @DISTRONAME@ system's underlying operating system. From here you can manage the entire system so you don't have to worry about what runs under the hood.[CR][CR]From here you can change your network connectivity, your keyboard layout and language and enable/disable remote access including Samba and SSH.</description>
    <description lang="es">Usa este add-on para administrar el sistema @DISTRONAME@. Desde aquí podrás controlar el sistema al completo (Conexiones de red, teclado, acceso remoto, samba y SSH)</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Usá esta extensión para administrar el sistema operativo subyacente a tu sistema @DISTRONAME@. Desde acá podés administrar el sistema en su totalidad sin tener que preocuparte por lo que pasa debajo del capó.[CR][CR]Desde acá podés cambiar la conexión de red, la distribución del teclado y el lenguaje y habilitar/deshabilitar el acceso remoto, incluyendo Samba y SSH.</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Usa este complemento para configurar el sistema operativo de tu @DISTRONAME@. Desde aquí puedes administrar todo el sistema fácilmente.[CR][CR]Desde aquí puedes cambiar la configuración de red, distribución del teclado, lenguaje del sistema y configurar Samba y SSH para controlar el acceso remoto al sistema.</description>
    <description lang="et">See  lisa on @DISTRONAME@ operatsioonisüsteemi häälestamiseks. Siit saad hallata kogu süsteemi, ilma et oleks vaja kaane alla piiluda.[CR][CR] Siit saab seada võrguühenduse parameetreid, klaviatuuripaigutust, keelt ning lubada/keelata kaugligipääsu, sealhulgas Samba ja SSH.</description>
    <description lang="fi">Käytä tätä lisäosaa muokataksesi @DISTRONAME@in alla olevaa käyttöjärjestelmää. Täältä voit muokata koko järjestelmää välittämättä siitä, mitä konepellin alta löytyy.[CR][CR]Voit muokata verkkoasetuksia, näppäimistön tyyppiä, kieliasetuksia sekä yhteysasetuksia, mukaanlukien Samba ja SSH.</description>
    <description lang="fr">Utilisez cette extension pour configurer votre système d'exploitation @DISTRONAME@. Vous pouvez gérer l'intégralité du système simplement sans vous soucier des détails techniques.[CR][CR]Vous pouvez modifier la connexion au réseau, la disposition du clavier ou la langue du système. Vous pouvez aussi activer les accès distants comme Samba ou SSH.</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Utilisez cet addiciel pour gérer le système d'exploitation sous-jacent de votre système @DISTRONAME@. D'ici vous pouvez gérer votre système au complet sans vous soucier de ce qui tourne sous la capot.[CR][CR]D'ici vous pouvez changer vos paramètres de connexion réseau, l'agencement et la langue de votre clavier et activer/désactiver l'accès distant incluant Samba et SSH.</description>
    <description lang="he">בעזרת הרחבה זו ניתן לנהל את מערכת ההפעלה של @DISTRONAME@. מכאן ניתן לנהל כל אחד ממאפייני המערכת כך שאין צורך לדאוג מה קורה מתחת לממשק המשתמש.[CR][CR]ניתן לשנות הגדרות רשת, מערך מקלדת ושפה וגם להפעיל/לנטרל שירותי גישה מרחוק כולל Samba ו-SSH.</description>
    <description lang="hr">Koristite ovaj dodatak za upravljanje @DISTRONAME@ operativnim sustavom. Odavdje možete upravljati cijelim sustavom stoga se ne morate brinuti što je pokrenuto u pozadini.[CR][CR]Odavdje možete promijeniti mrežno povezivenje, vaš raspored tipkovnice i jezik, omogućiti/onemogućiti udaljeni pristup uključujući Sambu i SSH.</description>
    <description lang="hu">Ez a kiegészítő vezérli az @DISTRONAME@ rendszer alatti operációs rendszer beállításait. Innen kezelheti a teljes rendszert, tehát nem szükséges aggódnia mi van a motorháztető alatt. [CR][CR] Innen állíthatóak be a hálózati kapcsolatok, billentyűzet kiosztás és nyelvezet valamint a távoli hozzáférések engedélyezése/letiltása beleértve a Samba-t és SSH-t is.</description>
    <description lang="it">Usa questo addon per gestire le impostazioni del sistema operativo di @DISTRONAME@. Da qui puoi gestire l'intero sistema senza necessità di una conoscenza avanzata del software sottostante.[CR][CR]Puoi modificare le connessioni di rete, il layout e la lingua della tastiera così come abilitare/disabilitare l'accesso remoto tramite Samba e SSH</description>
    <description lang="ja">このアドオンで@DISTRONAME@システムのオペレーティング・システムを管理します。ここからシステム全体を管理できますので、バックグラウンドで何が動作しているかなどを気にしなくてかまいません。[CR][CR]ネットワーク接続、キーボードのレイアウトや言語、SambaとSSHを含むリモートアクセスの有効・無効などの設定を行います。</description>
    <description lang="lt">Naudokite šį priedą operacines sistemos, kuris pagrįsta jūsų @DISTRONAME@ sistema, tvarkymui. Čia jūs galite valdyta visą sistemą, kad jums netektų rūpintis kas vyksta po gaubtu..[CR][CR]Čia galite pakeisti tinklo nustatymus, klaviatūros išdėstymą ir kalbą bei įjungti/išjungti nuotolinę prieigą, įskaitant Samba ir SSH.</description>
    <description lang="nl">Gebruik deze addon om het onderliggende @DISTRONAME@ systeem in te stellen. Vanaf hier kunt u het gehele systeem aanpassen, zodat u zich geen zorgen hoeft te maken over wat er onderhuids gebeurt.[CR][CR]Vanaf hier kunt u de netwerkverbindingen aanpassen, uw toetsenbord indeling en -taal, alsook een externe verbinding inclusief Samba en SSH in- of uitschakelen.</description>
    <description lang="no">Bruk dette tillegget for å konfigurere @DISTRONAME@s underliggende operativsystem. Herfra kan du konfigurere hele systemet slik at du ikke trenger å bekymre deg om hva som skjer under panseret.[CR][CR]Du kan endre nettverksinnstillinger, tastatur, språk og aktivere eller deaktivere nettverkstilgang slik som Samba og SSH.</description>
    <description lang="pl">Za pomocą tej wtyczki możesz zarządzać systemem @DISTRONAME@. Z tego miejsca masz kontrolę nad całym systemem.[CR][CR] Zarządzasz połączeniem sieciowym, układem klawiatury i językiem systemu oraz możesz włączyć lub wyłączyć dostęp zdalny, w tym Sambę i SSH.</description>
    <description lang="pt">Utilize este addon para gerir o sistema operativo que está na base do @DISTRONAME@. Aqui pode gerir todo o sistema, para não ter de se preocupar com aquilo que se passa nos bastidores.[CR][CR] Daqui, pode alterar as suas ligações de rede, disposição do teclado e idiomas. Também pode activar/desactivar acesso remoto, incluindo Samba e SSH.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Utilize este addon para gerenciar o sistema operacional do @DISTRONAME@. Aqui você pode gerenciar todo o sistema, para não ter de se preocupar com aquilo que se passa nos bastidores.[CR][CR] Daqui, você pode alterar as suas conexões de rede, configurações do teclado e idiomas. Também pode ativar/desativar acesso remoto, incluindo compartilhamento de rede do Windows e SSH.</description>
    <description lang="ru">Данное дополнение предназначено для управления системными настройками @DISTRONAME@. С помощью удобного интерфейса Вы можете управлять настройками системы (включая низкоуровневые настройки ОС) через удобный интерфейс.[CR][CR]Здесь Вы также сможете изменить способ соединения с сетью, настроить раскладку клавиатуры, выбрать язык интерфейса, а также включить удаленный доступ по SSH и/или Samba.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Tento doplnok slúži na správu operačného systému, na ktorom beží @DISTRONAME@. Odtiaľto je možné spravovať celý systém bez nutnosti znalostí o tom, čo beží pod kapotou.[CR][CR]Je tu možné meniť sieťové nastavenia, rozloženie a jazyk klávesnice alebo povoliť/zakázať vzdialený prístup prostredníctvom Samby a SSH.</description>
    <description lang="sl">S tem dodatkom upravljate operacijski sistem, ki deluje pod pokrovom sistema @DISTRONAME@. Odtod lahko upravljate s celotnim sistemom, tako da je skrb o tem, kar teče pod pokrovom, odveč.[CR][CR]Odtod lahko spremenite svojo omrežno povezljivost, postavitev tipkovnice in jezik ter omogočite/onemogočite oddaljeni dostop, vključno s Sambo in SSH.</description>
    <description lang="sv">Använd detta tillägg för att hantera ditt @DISTRONAME@-systems underliggande operativ. Härifrån kan du hantera hela systemet så du inte behöver oroa dig för vad som körs under skalet.[CR][CR]Härifrån kan du ändra din nätverksanslutning, tangentbordslayout och språk, samt aktivera/inaktivera fjärråtkomst inklusive Samba och SSH.</description>
    <description lang="tr">Bu eklentiyi kullanarak @DISTRONAME@ sisteminizin temelindeki işletim sistemini yönetin. Buradan tüm sistemi yönetebilirsiniz ve bu yüzden sistemin altında neler olduğu hakkında endişelenmenize gerek yok.[CR][CR]Buradan ağ bağlantısı, klavye düzeni ve dilini değiştirip, Samba ve SSH gibi uzaktan erişimi etkinleştirip/devre dışı bırakabilirsiniz.</description>
    <description lang="vi">Sử dụng addon này để quản lý  hệ thống điều hành @DISTRONAME@ cơ bản của bạn.&#10;Từ đây bạn có thể quản lý toàn bộ hệ thống, do đó bạn không cần phải lo lắng về những gì đang chạy . [CR][CR] Từ đây bạn có thể thay đổi kết nối mạng của bạn, bố trí bàn phím của bạn và ngôn ngữ và cho phép / vô hiệu hóa truy cập từ xa bao gồm Samba và SSH.</description>
    <description lang="zh">使用此插件管理你的 @DISTRONAME@ 系统的底层操作系统。它使你可以在无需深入了解的情况下管理整个系统。[CR][CR]在这里，你可以修改网络设置、键盘布局、语言以及启用/禁用 Samba 和 SSH 等远程访问功能。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
