<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.xperience1080" version="2.2.1" name="Xperience1080" provider-name="`Black">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="5.0.1" />
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.29" />
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="12.0.29" />
		<import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="6.0.10" />
		<import addon="script.tvtunes" version="4.4.6" />
		<import addon="script.globalsearch" version="2.0.8" />
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="5.0.2" />
		<import addon="script.artistslideshow" version="1.6.7" />
		<import addon="script.videolanguage" version="0.1.0" />
		<import addon="script.randomandlastitems" version="2.2.0" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1.00" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="bg">Обликът Xperience в 1080p вариант от Black</summary>
        <summary lang="cs">Black'ův 1080p mód Xperience skinu.</summary>
        <summary lang="de">Black's 1080p Mod des Xperience Skins</summary>
        <summary lang="el">Τροποποίηση (mod) ανάλυσης 1080p του Black για το κέλυφος Xperience</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Black's 1080p mod of the Xperience skin</summary>
        <summary lang="en_NZ">Black's 1080p mod of the Xperience skin</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">Black's 1080p mod of the Xperience skin</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Modificación 1080p del skin Xperience, por Black</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Mod en 1080p du thème Xperience par Black</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">Version en 1080p par Black de l'habillage Xperience</summary>
        <summary lang="gl">Modificación a 1080p do tema Xperience por Blackbolt</summary>
        <summary lang="he">Black's 1080p mod of the Xperience skin</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">Black 1080p mod az Xperience felszínhez</summary>
        <summary lang="it">Mod 1080p dello skin Xperience</summary>
        <summary lang="ko">Xperience 스킨을 Black이 1080p로 수정한 스킨</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">Black 1080 mod iš Xperience teminės išvaizdos</summary>
        <summary lang="ms">Kulir Xperience bagi mod Black 1080p</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Black's 1080p mod van de Xperience skin</summary>
        <summary lang="no">Black's 1080P versjon av Xperience-temaet</summary>
        <summary lang="pl"> Modyfikacja skórki Xperience autorstwa Black</summary>
        <summary lang="pt">O mod 1080p do tema Xperience, da autoria de Black</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Modificação em 1080p feita por Black do skin Xperience</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">1080p мод скина Xperience от Black</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Black's 1080p modifierinf av Xperience-skalet</summary>
        <summary lang="zh">Black制作的Xperience皮肤1080p修改版本</summary>
        <description lang="bg">Xperience1080 стартира като пълен 1080p вариант на Xperience облика на екипаBlackbolt. Междувременно той се променя толкова много, че в момента няма много общо с оригиналния Xperience облик. Xperience1080 предоставя облик с акцент върху качеството на графиката, плавните анимации и много добра интеграция на функции/добавки.</description>
        <description lang="cs">Xperience1080 začal čistě jako 1080p mód Xperience skinu skupinou Team Blackbolt. V průběhu času se skin změnil natolik, že v dnešní době už toho nemá moc společného s původním skinem Xperince . Xperience1080 je skin zaměřený na kvalitní grafické ztvárnění, hladké animace a velmi dobře propracovanou propojenost s doplňky.</description>
        <description lang="de">Xperience1080 startete als reiner 1080p Mod des Xperience Skins von Team Blackbolt. Mittlerweile wurde der Skin so grundlegend verändert, dass er mit dem originalen Xperience Skin nicht mehr viel gemein hat. Xperience1080 verspricht einen Skin mit hohem Anspruch auf grafische Qualität, flüssigen Animationen und optimal in den Skin integrierten Funktionen/Add-Ons.</description>
        <description lang="el">Το Xperience1080 ξεκίνησε σαν ένα απλό 1080p mod του κελύφους Xperience από την Team Blackbolt. Εν τω μεταξύ το κέλυφος άλλαξε εκ βάθρων σε σημείο που να μην έχει πλέον πολλά κοινά με το αρχικό Xperience. Το Xperience1080 είναι ένα κέλυφος που επικεντρώνεται στην οπτική ποιότητα, τις ομαλές μεταβάσεις και την πολύ καλή ενσωμάτωση λειτουργιών και πρόσθετων.</description>
        <description lang="en">Xperience1080 started as a pure 1080p mod of the Xperience skin by Team Blackbolt. In the meantime the skin changed fundamentally so it now hasn't much in common with the original Xperience skin. Xperience1080 delivers you a skin with focus on graphical quality, smooth animations and very well integrated functions/add-ons.</description>
        <description lang="en_NZ">Xperience1080 started as a pure 1080p mod of the Xperience skin by Team Blackbolt. In the meantime the skin changed fundamentally so it now hasn't much in common with the original Xperience skin. Xperience1080 delivers you a skin with focus on graphical quality, smooth animations and very well integrated functions/add-ons.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">Xperience1080 started as a pure 1080p mod of the Xperience skin by Team Blackbolt. In the meantime the skin changed fundamentally so it now hasn't much in common with the original Xperience skin. Xperience1080 delivers you a skin with focus on graphical quality, smooth animations and very well integrated functions/add-ons.</description>
        <description lang="es">Xperience1080 comenzó como una modificación a 1080p del skin Xperience por Team Blackbolt. Desde entonces, el skin ha cambiado tanto que ya no tiene mucho en común con el skin Xperience original. Xperience1080 le ofrece un skin centrado en la calidad gráfica, las transiciones fluidas y una gran integración con funciones/ complementos.</description>
        <description lang="fr">Xperience1080 a débuté comme un simple mod en 1080p du thème Xperience de la Team Blackbolt. Entre temps, le thème a fondamentalement changé et n'a à présent plus grand chose en commun avec le thème Xperience original. Xperience1080 vous offre un thème mettant l'accent sur ​​la qualité graphique, des animations fluides et une excellente intégration des fonctions/extensions.</description>
        <description lang="fr_CA">Xperience1080 a commencé comme une version en 1080p de l'habillage Xperience par l'équipe Blackbolt. Entre temps, l'habillage a changé fondamentalement et n'a maintenant plus grande chose à voir avec l'original. Xperience1080 vous offre un habillage qui se concentre sur la qualité graphique, la fluidité des animations et des fonctions/addiciels très bien intégrés.</description>
        <description lang="gl">Xperience1080 comezou coma unha modificación a só 1080p do tema Xperience polo equipo Blackbolt. Naqueles intres o tema mudou radicalmente e xa non ten nada en común co orixinal. Xperience1080 ofrécelle unha grande calidade gráfica, fermosas animacións e funcións e complementos ben integrados.</description>
        <description lang="he">Xperience1080 started as a pure 1080p mod of the Xperience skin by Team Blackbolt. In the meantime the skin changed fundamentally so it now hasn't much in common with the original Xperience skin. Xperience1080 delivers you a skin with focus on graphical quality, smooth animations and very well integrated functions/add-ons.</description>
        <description lang="hu">Az Xperience1080 egy letisztult 1080p mod az Xperience felszínből (Blackbolt). Az eredeti témához képest jelentősen megváltozott, így nem sok köze van az eredeti Xperience felszínhez. Az Xperience1080 fejlesztői a grafikai minőséget, a leggördülékenyebb animációkat és a lehető legjobban integrált extra kiegészítőket és funkciókat tartották szem előtt a felszín készítésekor.</description>
        <description lang="it">Xperience 1080 è partito come mod pura a 1080p dello skin Xperience del Team Blackbolt. Nel frattempo lo skin è cambiato profondamente cosi' ora non ha molto in comune con l'Xperience originale. Xperiece1080 ti consegna uno skin focalizzato sulla qualità della grafica, animazioni morbide e funzioni/add-ons molto ben integrate.</description>
        <description lang="ko">Xperience1080는 Xperience 스킨의 1080p 지원을 위한 Blackbolt팀의 수정판에서 시작하였습니다. 그동안 스킨은 근본적인 변화가 있었고 지금은 원래의 Xperience 스킨과 공통점이 거의 없습니다. Xperience1080는 높은 그래픽 품질, 부드러운 움직임, 기능과 애드온이 잘 통합된 스킨 환경을 제공합니다.</description>
        <description lang="lt">Xperience1080 buvo pradėtas kaip 1080p mod su Xperience teminės išvaizdos Blackbolt. Tuo tarpu teminė išvaizda iš esmės pasikeitė ir dabar ji neturi bendro su originalia Xperience temine išvaizda. Xperience1080 suteikia jums grafinę kokybę, sklandžią animaciją ir labai gerai integruotas Funkcijos/Priedai.</description>
        <description lang="ms">Xperience1080 bermula sebagai mod asli 1080p bagi kulit Xperience oleh Pasukan Blackbolt. Dalam tempoh perkembangannya kulit telah berubah secara asas dan kini banyak berubah dengan kulit Xperience yang asal. Xperience1080 menyediakan kulit yang berfokuskan pada kualiti grafik, animasi lancar dan fungsi/tambahan yang disepadukan dengan baik.</description>
        <description lang="nl">Xperience1080 begon als 1080p mod van Team Blackbolt's Xperience skin. Sindsdien is de skin drastisch gewijzigd, waardoor er weinig overeenkomsten meer zijn met de originele Xperience skin. Xperience1080 is een skin met nadruk op kwalitatieve grafische kwaliteit, vloeiende animaties en goede integratie met functionaliteit en add-ons.</description>
        <description lang="no">Xperience1080 startet som en ren 1080p modifikasjon av Xperience-temaet fra Team Blackbolt. Siden den gang har temaet endret seg fundamentalt, og har nå lite til felles med det orginale Xperience-temaet. Xperience1080 gir deg et tema med fokus på grafisk kvalitet, glatte animasjoner og svært godt integrerte funksjoner/tillegg.</description>
        <description lang="pl">Xperience1080 powstało jako modyfikacja skórki Xperience. Z biegiem czasu skóra zasadniczo się zmieniała, więc teraz nie ma wiele wspólnego z oryginalną skórką Xperience. Xperience1080 kładzie szczególny nacisk na jakość grafiki, animacji i bardzo dobrze zintegrowane funkcje oraz dodatki.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Xperience1080 começou como uma modificação puramente em 1080p da skin Xperience do Time Blackbolt. Ao passar do tempo, a skin mudou fundamentalmente então não há muito em comum com a original. Xperience1080 traz a você uma skin com foco em qualidade gráfica, animações suaves e funções e add-ons bem integrados.</description>
        <description lang="ru">Изначально скин Xperience1080 был создан как адаптация скина Xperience от Team Blackbolt под 1080p. Однако со временем он кардинально изменился и сейчас в нем осталось не так много от своего предка. Xperience1080 спроектирован с упором на высочайшее качество графики, гладкость анимации и хорошую интеграцию функционала и дополнений.</description>
        <description lang="sv">Xperience1080 började som en ren 1080p modifiering av Xperience-skalet av Team Blackbolt. Under tiden ändrades skalet så pass mycket att det nu inte har mycket gemensamt med originalskalet. Xperience1080 ger dig ett skal med focus på grafisk kvalitet, mjuka animationer och välintegrerade funktioner/tillägg.</description>
        <description lang="zh">Xperience1080是Blackbolt小组发起的基于Xperience皮肤的纯面向1080p分辨率修改版. 在发展期间, 皮肤发生了一些本质的变化, 所以现在与原始的Xperience皮肤并没有太多共同之处了. Xperience1080 为你提供一个注重图片质量, 顺滑动画和优质的集成功能/插件的皮肤.</description>
        <disclaimer lang="de">Nur kompatibel mit Kodi 13.x "Gotham".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el">Συμβατό μόνο με την έκδοση Kodi 13.x "Gotham".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Compatible with Kodi 13.x "Gotham" only.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Compatible with Kodi 13.x "Gotham" only.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_US">Compatible with Kodi 13.x "Gotham" only.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es">Solo compatible con Kodi 13.x "Gotham".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr">Compatible avec Kodi 13.x "Gotham" uniquement.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Compatible seulement avec Kodi 13.x « Gotham ».</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="gl">Solo compatible con Kodi 13.x "Gotham"</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="he">תואם גרסת "Kodi 13.x "Gotham בלבד.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hu">Csak az Kodi 13.x "Gotham"-val kompatibilis</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="it">Compatibile solo con Kodi 13.x "Gotham"</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ko">Kodi 13.x "Gotham"에서만 사용할 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="lt">Suderinama tik su Kodi 13.x "Gotham".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ms">Serasi dengan Kodi 13.x "Gotham" sahaja.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="nl">Alleen compatibel met Kodi 13.x "Gotham".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pl">Skóra kompatybilna wyłącznie z Kodi 13.x "Gotham".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Compatível somente com Kodi 13.0 "Gotham".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ru">Совместим только с последними сборками Kodi 13.x "Gotham".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sv">Endast kompatibelt med Kodi 13.x "Gotham".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh">仅与 Kodi 13.x "Gotham" 版本兼容。</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-Share Alike 3.0</license>
        <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=146690</forum>
        <email>xperience1080 at iCloud dot com</email>
        <source>https://github.com/Black09/Xperience1080</source>
	</extension>
</addon>
