<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='yes'?>
<addon id="plugin.video.vimeo" name="Vimeo" provider-name="TheCollective" version="3.5.2">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="2.5.1" />
    <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="1.9.4" />
  </requires>
  <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
        <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">Видео добавка за Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Modul videa Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Vimeo video plug-in</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Vimeo video plugin</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Plugin βίντεο Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Vimeo video plugin</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Plugin de video de Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Plugin de video Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Vimeo videó kiegészítő</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Plugin Video Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Vimeo додаток за видеа</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Vimeo videoplugin</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wtyczka wideo Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Plugin de vídeo Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Plugin de vídeo do Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Видео-плагин Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Vimeo video doplnok</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Vimeo videotillägg</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">Vimeo视频插件</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">Vimeo視頻外掛插件</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Добавката ви позволява да разглеждате и гледате видео клипове от любимия на всички алтернативен видео сайт!</description>
    <description lang="cs">Modul, který vám umožní procházet a přehrávat videa z nejoblíbenější alternativní stránky videí.</description>
    <description lang="da">Plug-in</description>
    <description lang="de">Plugin welches ermöglicht, Videos von jedermanns Lieblingsalternativplattform zu durchsuchen und anzusehen</description>
    <description lang="el">Ένα plugin που σας επιτρέπει να περιηγηθείτε και να δείτε βίντεο από την πιο αγαπημένη εναλλακτική ιστοσελίδα βίντεο!</description>
    <description lang="en">Plugin that allows you to browse and view videos from everybodys favorite alternative video site!</description>
    <description lang="es">Plugin que te permite navegar y ver videos desde el sitio alternativo favorito de todo el mundo!</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Plugin que permite listar y ver videos del sitio de videos alternativo que gusta a todo el mundo</description>
    <description lang="hu">A kiegészítő segítségével videókat böngészhetsz és játszhatsz le mindenki kedvenc alternatív videó oldaláról!</description>
    <description lang="it">Plugin che permette di sfogliare e vedere video dal sito alternativo preferito di tutti il video!</description>
    <description lang="mk">Додаток кој ви овозможува да прелистувате и гледате видеа од сајтот Vimeo</description>
    <description lang="nl">Plugin waarmee je video's kunt zoeken en bekijken van ieders favoriete alternatieve videosite! </description>
    <description lang="pl">Wtyczka pozwala na wyszukiwanie i oglądanie wideo z ulubionej przez wszystkich alternatywnej strony wideo!</description>
    <description lang="pt">Um plugin que permite navegar e ver vídeos no site alternativo de vídeo que todos preferem.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Plugin que permite que você navegue e veja vídeos do site alternativo de vídeos favorito de todo mundo!</description>
    <description lang="ru">Плагин который позволяет просматривать видео с лучшего альтернативного видео сайта!</description>
    <description lang="sk">Doplnok, ktorý umožňuje prehliadanie a pozeranie videí z obľúbenej alternatívnej vide stránky!</description>
    <description lang="sv">Tillägg som låter dig bläddra och visa videor från allas favoritalternativvideosajt!</description>
    <description lang="zh">使你能从大家喜爱的视频站点浏览和观看视频的插件！</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">可以讓您多了一個選擇從人人上傳最愛視頻的影片網站瀏覽及檢視影片的外掛插件</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
