<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.dump" name="Dump.com" version="2.0.1" provider-name="Tristan Fischer (sphere@dersphere.de)">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
        <import addon="script.module.xbmcswift2" version="2.4.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="addon.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="be">Family Friendly Videos</summary>
        <summary lang="bg">Видеозаписи подходящи за цялото семейство</summary>
        <summary lang="ca">Videos Familiars </summary>
        <summary lang="da">Familievenlige Videoer</summary>
        <summary lang="de">Familienfreundliche Videos</summary>
        <summary lang="el">Βίντεο για όλη την Οικογένεια</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Family Friendly Videos</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Videos de ambiente familiar</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Vidéos pour toute la famille</summary>
        <summary lang="gl">Vídeos de Ambiente Familiar</summary>
        <summary lang="he">סרטונים הולמים לכל הגילאים</summary>
        <summary lang="hr">Obiteljske video snimke</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">Családbarát videók</summary>
        <summary lang="id">Video Ramah Keluarga</summary>
        <summary lang="it">Video per la Famiglia</summary>
        <summary lang="ko">가족 중심의 비디오</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Familie Vriendelijke Video's</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Wideo przyjazne rodzinie</summary>
        <summary lang="pt">Vídeos Para Toda a Família</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Vídeos apropriados para toda a Família</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Видео для семейного просмотра</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Familjevänliga videor</summary>
        <summary lang="ta_IN">குடும்பத்தோடு பார்க்ககூடிய வீடியோக்கள்</summary>
        <summary lang="zh">家庭视频</summary>
        <description lang="be">Website containing interesting, educational and funny videos that are suitable for all ages. Updated daily.</description>
        <description lang="bg">Уебсайт с интересни, образователи и забавни видео записи, подходящи за всяка възраст. Съдържанието се обновява ежедневно.</description>
        <description lang="ca">Lloc web que conté vídeos interessants, educatiUS i divertiTS que són adequats per a totes les edats. Actualitzat diàriament.</description>
        <description lang="da">Webside med interessante, belærende og sjove videoer der er passende for alle aldre. Opdateret dagligt.</description>
        <description lang="de">Die Webseite enthält interessante, lehrreiche und lustige Videos für Zuschauer jeden Alters. Tägliche Updates</description>
        <description lang="el">Ιστοσελίδα ενδιαφερόντων, εκπαιδευτικών και αστείων βίντεο κατάλληλων για όλες τις ηλικίες. Καθημερινές ενημερώσεις.</description>
        <description lang="en">Website containing interesting, educational and funny videos that are suitable for all ages. Updated daily.</description>
        <description lang="es">Sitio web que contiene vídeos interesantes, educativos y divertidos que son adecuados para todas las edades. Actualizado diariamente.</description>
        <description lang="fr">Site web contenant des vidéos intéressantes, éducatives et drôles sans limite d'âge. Mises à jour quotidienne.</description>
        <description lang="gl">Sitio web que contén vídeos interesantes, educativos e divertidos, sendo os máis axeitados a todas as idades. Actualizado ao día.</description>
        <description lang="he">אתר המכיל סרטונים מעניינים, מחכימים ומצחיקים המתאימים לכל הגילאים. מתעדכן באופן יומיומי.</description>
        <description lang="hr">Web stranica sadrži zanimljive, obrazovne i zabavne video snimke koje su prikladne za sve uzraste. Dnevno se ažurira.</description>
        <description lang="hu">Érdekes, oktató és vidám videók minden korosztály számára. Napi frissítéssel.</description>
        <description lang="id">Situs web berisi video yang menarik, edukatif dan lucu yang cocok untuk semua usia. Diperbarui setiap hari.</description>
        <description lang="it">Il Sito contiene video interessanti, educativi e divertenti adatti a tutte le età. Aggiornamenti giornalieri.</description>
        <description lang="ko">웹사이트는 모든 연령대에 적합한 흥미롭고 교육적이며 재미있는 비디오로 구성되어 있습니다. 매일 업데이트됩니다.</description>
        <description lang="nl">Website bevat interessante, educatieve en grappige video's die geschikt zijn voor alle leeftijden. Dagelijks bijgewerkt.</description>
        <description lang="pl">Strona zawierająca interesujące, rozwijające i zabawne wideo, odpowiednie dla wszsystkich grup wiekowych. Aktualizowane codziennie.</description>
        <description lang="pt">Um site que contém vídeos interessantes, educativos e divertidos, apropriados para todas as idades. Actualizado diariamente.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Site com conteúdos interessantes, vídeos educativos e engraçados que são adequados para todas as idades. Atualizado diariamente.</description>
        <description lang="ru">Сайт содержит познавательные и забавные видео, подходящие для всех возрастов. Обновляется ежедневно.</description>
        <description lang="sv">Webbsidan innehåller intressanta, utbildande och roliga videor som är lämpliga för alla åldrar. Uppdaterad dagligen.</description>
        <description lang="ta_IN">அனைத்து வயதினருக்கும் ஏற்ற சுவாரஸ்யமான, கல்வி மற்றும் வேடிக்கையான வீடியோக்களை கொண்ட இணையத்தளம். தினசரி புதுப்பிக்கப்பட்டது.</description>
        <description lang="zh">包含适合所有年龄段观众的有趣、有教育意义和搞笑视频的网站。每日更新。</description>
        <language />
        <platform>
        <website>http://www.dump.com/</website>
        <source>https://github.com/dersphere/plugin.video.dump</source>
        <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=126088</forum>
        <email>sphere@dersphere.de</email>
        <license>GNU GENERAL PUBLIC LICENSE. Version 2, June 1991</license>
    </extension>
</addon>
