<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="plugin.audio.spotlight" version="SPOTLIGHT_VERSION" name="Spotlight" provider-name="Dariusz Biskup">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="ui_addon.py">
        <provides>audio</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service"
             library="server_addon.py" start="startup">
	</extension>             
    <extension point="xbmc.service"
             library="login_addon.py" start="login">
	</extension>             
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="bg">Представени</summary>
        <summary lang="ca">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="cs">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="de">Rampenlicht</summary>
        <summary lang="el">Τυχαία</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="en_AU">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="en_NZ">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Destacadas</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Recommandés</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">Sous les spots</summary>
        <summary lang="gl">Salientados</summary>
        <summary lang="he">ספוטלייט</summary>
        <summary lang="hr">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">Kiemelt</summary>
        <summary lang="it">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="ko">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="ms">Sorotan</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="no">Søkelyset</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="pt">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Em foco</summary>
        <summary lang="ro">În lumina reflectoarelor</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Сцена</summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="th">รายการเด่น</summary>
        <summary lang="tr">Spotlight</summary>
        <summary lang="zh">Spotlight</summary>
        <description lang="ca">Complement de Spotify per Kodi utilitzant els menús nadius de Kodi. Permet la cerca de pistes, llistant per: llistes de reproducció, artistes, pistes, pistes marcades com a preferides i reproducció i posada en cua de pistes, àlbums etc. Es pot manipular via client mòbil com ara el Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="cs">Doplněk Spotify  pro Kodi používá nativní systém menu Kodi.&#10;Umožňuje hledání stop, zobrazení: playlistů, alb pro umělce,&#10;stop alba, sledovaných stop, přehrávání a  řazení stop do fronty atd. Vše je možno ovládat také pomocí mobilní aplikace např. Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="de">Das Spotify AddOn für Kodi verwendet native Kodi Menüs. Es erlaubt das Suchen nach Titel. Es zeigt Wiedergabelisten, Künstler, Alben und begonnen, spielende und folgende Titel usw. an. Es kann mobil mit einem Client, der ähnlich wie Yaste ist, betrieben werden.</description>
        <description lang="el">Το πρόσθετο Spotify για το Kodi αξιοποιεί τα υπάρχοντα μενού του Kodi. Επιτρέπει την αναζήτηση κομματιών, λιστών αναπ/γής, άλμπουμ καλλιτεχνών, κομματιών άλμπουμ, κομματιών με αστέρι, αναπαραγωγή και τοποθέτηση αυτών σε αναμονή, κτλ. Μπορείτε να το χειριστείτε και μέσω εφαρμογών κινητών όπως το Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="en">Spotify add-on for Kodi using native Kodi menus. It allows searching for tracks, listing: playlists, artist albums, album tracks, starred tracks and playing and queueing tracks, albums etc. It can be operated via mobile client like Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="en_NZ">Spotify add-on for Kodi using native Kodi menus. It allows searching for tracks, listing: playlists, artist albums, album tracks, starred tracks and playing and queueing tracks, albums etc. It can be operated via mobile client like Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">Spotify add-on for Kodi using native Kodi menus. It allows searching for tracks, listing: playlists, artist albums, album tracks, starred tracks and playing and queueing tracks, albums etc. It can be operated via mobile client like Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="es">Addon de Spotify para Kodi que usa los menúes nativos de Kodi. Permite buscar pistas, listas de reproducción, listar álbumes por intérprete, canciones por álbum, canciones preferidas y reproducir y encolar pistas, álbumes, etc. Puede ser operado con aplicaciones móviles como Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="fr">L'add-on Spotify pour Kodi utilise les menus Kodi d'origine. Il permet de chercher des pistes, lister: playlistes, albums d'un artiste, les pistes d'un album, noter les pistes et jouer une liste de pistes, albums etc. Cela peut-être effectué par un client mobile comme Yatse</description>
        <description lang="fr_CA">Addiciel Spotify pour Kodi utilisant les menus natifs de Kodi. Il permet de chercher des pistes, lister des listes de lecture, des albums d'artistes, des pistes d'albums, des pistes favorites et de jouer et mettre dans la file de lecture et dans la file d'attente des pistes, des albums, etc. Il peut être mis en action par un client mobile comme Yatze.</description>
        <description lang="gl">Complemento para o Kodi do Spotify. Permite a busca de pistas listando por: listaxes de reprodución, álbums de artistas, pistas do álbum, pistas puntuadas e pistas en reprodución ou en cola, álbums, etc. Pódese controlar mediante un cliente para móbil como Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="hr">Spotify dodatak za Kodi koristi izvorne Kodi izbornike. Omogućuje pretraživanje pjesama, prikaz: popisa izvođenja, izvođača albuma, brojeve pjesama, ocjene pjesama, reproducirane pjesme i pjesme na redoslijedu reprodukcije, albume itd. Može se upravljati putem mobitela klijentom poput Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="it">L'add-on Spotify per Kodi usa l'interfaccia di Kodi. Ti permette di cercare le tracce, liste: playlist, album di artisti, tracce di artisti, tracce valutate, riprodurre ed accodare le tracce, album ecc... può essere usata tramite un dispositivo mobile con Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="lt">Spotify priedas skirtas Kodi bei naudojantis įprastus Kodi meniu. Jis leidžia ieškoti takelių, atvaizduoti grojaraščius, atlikėjo albumus, albumo takelius, žvaigždute pažymėtus takelius ir atkurti bei pridėti į atkūrimo eilę takelius, albumus ir kt. elementus. Jį galima valdyti naudojant mobilius klientus, tokius kaip Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="nl">Spotify add-on voor Kodi met behulp van de standaard Kodi menu's. Het maakt het zoeken naar nummers, en lijsten: afspeellijsten, artiest albums, album nummers, starred nummers, speelduur, wachtrij nummers en albums enz. Het kan via een mobiele cliënt zoals Yatse worden bediend.</description>
        <description lang="no">Spotify tillegg for Kodi som benytter Kodi menyer. Her kan du søke etter sanger, spillelister, albumer, favorittsanger etc. Alt kan kontrolleres via en mobilklient som Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="pl">Dodatek Spotify dla Kodi używa wbudowanych menu Kodi. Umożliwia wyszukiwanie utworów, odtwarzanie według: list odtwarzania, albumów wykonawcy, albumów, ulubionych utworów oraz kolejkowanie utworów, albumów itp. Dodatek ten można obsługiwać za pomocą mobilnego klienta takiego jak Yatse. </description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Add-on Spotify para o Kodi usa menus nativos. Permite procura por faixas, ouvir: listas de reprodução, álbuns do artista, faixas do álbum, faixas preferidas e reprodução e enfileirar faixas, álbuns etc. Pode ser operado remotamente via um cliente como o controle remoto Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="sv">Spotify-tillägg för Kodi som använder ursprungliga Kodi-menyer. Du kan söka efter låtar, lista: spellistor, artister, album, stjärnmärkta låtar och spela och kölägga låtar, album etc. Tillägget kan styras ifrån mobilklienter såsom Yatse.</description>
        <description lang="zh">Spotify 插件使用 Kodi 原生菜单。支持搜索歌曲，列出播放列表、歌手专辑、专辑曲目、星级曲目，以及播放和将歌曲、专辑等加入播放队列。可以象 Yatse 那样通过手机客户端来操作。</description>
        <disclaimer lang="ca">Necesita una compta Spotify Premium.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="cs">Je třeba mít Spotify Premium účet.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de">Erfordert ein Spotify Premium-Konto.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el">Απαιτείται λογαριασμός Spotify Premium.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en">It requires a Spotify Premium account.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">It requires a Spotify Premium account.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_US">It requires a Spotify Premium account.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es">Requiere cuenta Premium de Spotify.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr">Nécessite un compte Spotify Premium</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Il exige un compte Spotify Premium.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="gl">Requirese dunha conta Premium no Spotify.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="he">דורש חשבון פרימיום של Spotify.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hr">Potreban je Spotify Premium račun.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="it">Richiede un account Premium di Spotify.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="lt">Reikalinga Spotify Premium paskyra.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="nl">Het vereist een Spotify premium account.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="no">Spotiify Premium konto kreves.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pl">Wymagane konto Spotify Premium.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt">É necessário possuir uma conta Spotify Premium.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Requer uma conta Spotify Premium.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sv">Ett Spotify Premium-konto krävs.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="tr">Bu Spotify Premium hesabı gerektirir.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh">需要一个 Spotify 的高级帐户。</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>
