<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="metadata.artists.universal"
       name="Universal Artist Scraper"
       version="2.1.8"
       provider-name="Team XBMC">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.metadata" version="1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.last.fm" version="1.5.1"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.allmusic.com" version="2.5.2"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.musicbrainz.org" version="1.2.1"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.htbackdrops.com" version="1.2.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.fanart.tv" version="1.1.0"/>
    <import addon="metadata.common.theaudiodb.com" version="1.2.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.metadata.scraper.artists"
             language="en"
             library="artistuniversal.xml"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">Универсален източник за информация за артисти</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Arreplegador universal per artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Univerzální zdroj získávání dat pro umělce</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Universel scraper til kunstnere</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Universal Scraper für Interpreten</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Scraper universal para artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="es_MX">Scraper Universal de Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Collecteur universel d'artistes</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Universal Scraper for Artists</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Universalus Artistų Scrapers</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Universal Scraper dla Artystów muzycznych</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Scraper Universal para Artistas</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Univerzálny zdroj získavania dát pre umelcov</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Universiell artistskrapa</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">通用艺术家信息刮削器</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля информация от следните сайтове: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com. Изобрания извлича от: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. Можете да определите от кой сайт каква информация да се сваля.&#10;&#10;Първоначалното търсене винаги се прави в MusicBrainz. Когато не е налична препратка към allmusic.com на сайта на MusicBrainz извличането на информация от allmusic.com става невъзможно (добавянето на препратка е много лесно).</description>
    <description lang="ca">Aquest arreplegador recull informació dels següents llocs suportats</description>
    <description lang="cs">Tento zdroj dat získává informace z následujících podporovaných stránek: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Lze nastavit jakou informaci stahovat z jakých stránek.&#10;&#10;Základní hledání je vždy provedeno na MusicBrainz. V případě, že schází odkaz allmusic na stránce MusicBrains, nelze stáhnout informace z allmusic.com (avšak je velmi snadné chybějící odkazy přidat).</description>
    <description lang="da">Denne scraper samler information fra følgende sider: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, og allmusic.com, og henter illustrationer fra: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm og allmusic.com. Den kan sættes felt for felt fra de sider du nu måtte ønske at få de pågældende informationer fra.&#10;&#10;Den første søgning er altid på MusicBrainz. Hvis ikke allmusic linket er tilføjet på MusicBrainz side, kan felter fra allmusic.com ikke hentes (men det er helt enkelt at tilføje de manglende links).</description>
    <description lang="de">Dieser Scraper unterstützt das Sammeln von Informationen von den folgenden Seiten: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, und allmusic.com, Grafiken werden geladen von: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm und allmusic.com. Es kann Feld für Feld festgelegt werden welche Information von welcher Seite geladen werden soll.&#10;&#10;Die erste Suche wird immer auf  MusicBrainz durchgeführt. Sollte der allmusic link auf der MusicBrainz Seite fehlen, können keine Informationen von allmusic geladen werden. (diese fehlenden links können sehr leicht nachgetragen werden).</description>
    <description lang="en">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="es">Este scraper recolecta información de las siguientes webs: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene las imágenes de fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Permite especificar de qué web se quiere obtener la información específica. ⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial se realiza siempre en MusicBrainz. En caso de que los enlaces a allmusic no estén añadidos en la web de MusicBrainz, no se podrán obtener los campos de información de este sitio (aunque es muy fácil añadir esos enlaces que faltan).</description>
    <description lang="es_MX">Este scraper obtiene información de los siguientes sitios soportados: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm y allmusic.com, mientras obtiene artwork de: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm y allmusic.com. Puede ser configurado campo por campo de que sitio quieres esa información específica.⏎ ⏎ La búsqueda inicial siempre es hecha en MusicBrainz. En el caso en que los enlaces de allmusic no son agregados en el sitio de  MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com no pueden ser obtenidos. (De cualquier manera es muy fácil agregar esos enlaces no encontrados).</description>
    <description lang="fr">Ce collecteur répertorie les informations des sites suivants : TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, Last.fm et allmusic.com tout en assemblant les illustrations depuis : fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm et allmusic.com. Vous pouvez définir la source d'information pour chaque champ.&#10;&#10;La recherche initiale est toujours faite à partir de MusicBrainz. xxxxxxxx (en attente du retour de l'équipe xbmc) xxxxxxxxxxx</description>
    <description lang="ko">This scraper collects information from the following supported sites: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, and allmusic.com, while grabs artwork from: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm and allmusic.com. It can be set field by field that from which site you want that specific information.&#10;&#10;The initial search is always done on MusicBrainz. In case allmusic link is not added on the MusicBrainz site fields from allmusic.com cannot be fetched (very easy to add those missing links though).</description>
    <description lang="lt">Šis Scrapers renka informaciją iš šių palaikomų svetainių: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm, ir allmusic.com, ir atsiunčia meno kūrinius iš: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm ir allmusic.com. Jis gali būti nustatyti lauko srityje, kurioje svetainėje norite, kad konkrečiu atveju pradinė informacijos pradinis paieška visada bus atlikta remiantis MusicBrainz. Allmusic nuoroda įdėta į MusicBrainz vietoje laukų allmusic.com negali būti (nors tas trūkstamas grandis labai lengva įtraukti).</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Este scraper coleta informações nos seguintes sites:&#10;MusicBrainz, last.fm, allmusic.com e amazon.de, enquanto pega os artwork de: fanart.tv, last.fm and allmusic.com. O Mesmo pode ser configurara campo a campo em que site você quer obter informações específicas. A procura inicial é sempre feita no MusicBrainz. No caso allmusic e/ou amazon.de não terem sido adicionados no site MusicBrainz, campos de allmusic.com e/ou amazona.de não serão buscados (embora seja muito fácil adicionar os links faltantes). </description>
    <description lang="sk">Tento zdroj získavania dát zbiera infomácie z nasledujúcich podporovaných stránok: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm a allmusic.com. Grafiku získava zo stránok: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm a allmusic.com. Je možné podrobne nastaviť, z ktorej stránky chcete získať konkrétne informácie.&#10;&#10;Počiatočné hľadanie je vždy na stránke MusicBrainz. V prípade, že odkaz pre allmusic nie je pridaný na stránku MusicBrainz, nie je možné získať údaje zo stránky allmusic.com (je ale veľmi jednoduché tieto chýbajúce odkazy pridať).</description>
    <description lang="sv">Denna skrapa samlar information från följande sajter: TheAudioDb.com, MusicBrainz, last.fm och allmusic.com, medans den samlar konstverk från: fanart.tv, htbackdrops.com, last.fm och allmusic.com. Du kan ange fält för fält från vilken sajt du vill ha den specifika inforamtionen från. Den initiala sökningen är alltid gjord på MusicBrainz. Om inte allmusic.com länken läggs till på MusicBrainz sajten, kan inte fält från allmusic.com hämtas (väldigt enkelt att lägga till dom saknade länkarna dock).</description>
    <description lang="zh">本刮削器支持从以下网站获取信息：TheAudioDb.com、MusicBrainz、last.fm和allmusic.com，并从以下网站获取艺术图片：fanart.tv、htbackdrops.com、last.fm和allmusic.com。你可以指定每一项内容的来源网站。&#10;&#10;初始结果总是先从MusicBrainz获取，如果MusicBrainz网站未加入到allmusic的外部链接，则无法获取allmusic.com的信息（当然你能很容易地加入缺失的链接）。</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
