<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon 
	id="skin.nbox"
	version="1.0.1"
	name="nbox"
	provider-name="Niamu">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0"/>
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.14"/>
	</requires>
	<extension
		point="xbmc.gui.skin"
		defaultthemename="Textures.xbt"
		debugging="false"
		effectslowdown="1.00">
		<res width="1280" height="720" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="720p" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary lang="bg">Изчистен и опростен дизайн. Оригиналният Lightbox облик е от Tree Jammer - модифициран от Niamu под името nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="de">Ein knappes und und einfaches Design. Original Lightbox-Skin von Tree_Jammer - von Niamu als nbox modifiziert</summary>
		<summary lang="el">Ένας ελαφρύς και απλός σχεδιασμός. Το αρχικό κέλυφος Lightbox από τον Tree_Jammer - τροποποιημένο από τον Niamu με το όνομα nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="en">A lean and simple design. Original Lightbox skin by Tree_Jammer - modified by Niamu as nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="en_NZ">A lean and simple design. Original Lightbox skin by Tree_Jammer - modified by Niamu as nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Un diseño ajustado y simple. El skin original Lighbox de Tree_Jammer - modificado por Niamu como nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Un design simple et allongé. Apparence originale de Lightbox par Tree_Jammer - modifié en nbox par Niamu</summary>
		<summary lang="fr_CA">Une conception simple et légere. Habillage originale Lightbox par Tree_Jammer - modifié par Niamu en nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="gl">Un deseño limpo e simple. Tema Lightbox por Tree_Jammer - modificado por Niamu como nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="hu">Egyszerű és minimalista design. Az eredeti Lightbox felszín (Tree_Jammer) - módosított verziója Niamu által, ez az nbox.</summary>
		<summary lang="ms">Rekabentuk yang ringkas dan nipis. Kulit Lightbox asal oleh Tree_Jammer - diubahsuai oleh Niamu sebagai nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="nl">Een klein en simpel ontwerp. Orginele Lightbox skin van Tree_Jammer - gemodificeerd door Niamu als nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Odchudzony i prosty wygląd. Oryginalna skóra Lightbox Tree_Jammera - modyfikowana do nbox przez Niamu</summary>
		<summary lang="pt">Com um design simples e humilde. O tema original, Lightbox, é da autoria de Tree_Jammer e foi modificado por Niamu para se tornar no nbox.</summary>
		<summary lang="pt_BR">Um design simples e definido. Do skin original Lightbox de Tree_Jammer - modificado por Niamu como nbox</summary>
		<summary lang="ru">nbox это обложка с простым и лаконичным дизайном на основе Lightbox (авт. Tree_Jammer), модификации Niamu. </summary>
		<summary lang="sv">En slimmad och enkel design. Originalet, Lightbox skin, skapat av Tree-Jammer - modifierad av Niamu som nbox </summary>
		<summary lang="zh">以简洁易用为设计目标. 源自Tree_Jammer 开发的Lightbox  - 后来由 Niamu 修改成为 nbox .</summary>
		<description lang="bg">nbox е проектиран да показва само това от което се нуждаете фокусирайки се върху скоростта и изчистения дизайн. Първоначално създаден от Tree Jammer и по-късно модифициран от Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="de">nbox wurde designed um dir nur das zu zeigen, was du brauchst mit einem Fokus auf Schnelligkeit und Klarheit. Urpsrünglich erstellt von Tree_Jammer und später modifiziert von Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="el">Το nbox είναι σχεδιασμένο να εμφανίζει μόνο ότι χρειάζεστε, δίνοντας έμφαση στην ταχύτητα και την ακρίβεια. Το αρχικό κέλυφος δημιουργήθηκε από τον Tree_Jammer και αργότερα τροποποιήθηκε από τον Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="en">nbox is designed to show only what you need with a focus on speed and clarity. Originally created by Tree_Jammer and later modified by Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="en_NZ">nbox is designed to show only what you need with a focus on speed and clarity. Originally created by Tree_Jammer and later modified by Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="es">NBOX está diseñado para mostrar sólo lo que necesitas, con un enfoque en la velocidad y claridad. Originalmente creado por Tree_Jammer y posteriormente modificado por Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="fr">nbox a été créé dans le but de ne vous montrer que l'essentiel avec rapidité et clarté. Créé à l'origine par Tree_Jammer et modifié plus tard par Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="fr_CA">nbox est conçu pour montrer seulement ce dont vous avez besoin avec un accent sur la vitesse et la clarté. Créé à l'origine par Tree_Jammer et modifié ultérieurement par Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="gl">nbox esta deseñado para amosarlle só o que necesita poñendo o foco na velocidade e na claridade. Creado na súa orixe por Tree_Jammer e modificado despois por Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="hu">Az nbox felszínt azért tervezték, hogy a sebesség és átláthatóság legyen a fókuszban. Eredeti szerző Tree_Jammer , később Niamu módosította.</description>
		<description lang="ms">nbox direka untuk hanya tunjukkan apa yang anda perlukan dengan fokus pada kelajuan dan kejelasan. Asalnya dicipta oleh Tree_Jammer dan kemudian diubahsuai oleh Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="nl">nbox is ontworpen om je alleen  te laten zien wat je nodig heb met focus op snelheid en helderheid. van origine ontworpen door Tree_Jammer en later gemodificeerd door Niamu</description>
		<description lang="pl">nbox jest opracowany by pokazywać jedynie to, co potrzebne, mając na celu prędkość oraz przejrzystość. Stworzony przez Tree_Jammera, a następnie modyfikowany przez Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="pt">O nbox foi construído para mostrar-lhe apenas aquilo que precisa, com rapidez e clareza. O tema original é da autoria de Tree_Jammer e foi modificado mais tarde por Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="pt_BR">nbox foi projetado para exibir somente o que você precisa focado em velocidade e clareza. Criado originalmente por Tree_Jammer e modificado mais tarde por Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="ru">nbox показывает только необходимую информацию с целью сохранения максимальной скорости работы  и простоты использования. Исходная версия  - Tree_Jammer, модификации - Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="sv">nbox är designat för att visa endast vad du behöver med ett fokus på snabbhet och klarhet. Ursprungligen skapad av Tree_Jammer och senare modifierad av Niamu.</description>
		<description lang="zh">nbox 设计为只显示你需要的信息, 着眼于速度和明快.  最初为 Tree_Jammer 创建, 后来由 Niamu 修改.</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>
