<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon
    id="script.artwork.downloader"
    name="Artwork Downloader"
    version="12.0.29"
    provider-name="Martijn"
    >
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python"                 version="2.1.0"/>
    <import addon="xbmc.json"                   version="6.0.0"/>
    <import addon="xbmc.addon"                  version="12.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simplejson"    version="3.3.0"/>
    <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache"  version="1.3.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.script"         library="default.py">
    <provides>executable</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="be">Downloads Artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library</summary>
    <summary lang="bg">Сваля изображения за филми, ТВ Сериали и музикални клипове</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Descarrega il·lustracions de sèries de TV, pel·lícules i vídeos musicals a la teva biblioteca</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Stáhne artworky pro seriály, filmy a hudební videa ve vaší knihovně</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Downloader grafik til TV-serier, Film og Musikvideoer i dit bibliotek</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Lädt Artworks für Fernsehshows, Filme und Musikvideos in deine Bibliothek herunter</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Κατεβάζει Εικόνες για τις Τηλεοπτικές Σειρές, τις Ταινίες και τα Μουσικά Βίντεο της συλλογής σας</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Downloads Artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library</summary>
    <summary lang="en_AU">Downloads Artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Downloads Artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Downloads Artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Descargue Artwork de Series, Pelí­culas y Videoclips a su biblioteca</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Collecte les illustrations des séries TV, films et clips vidéo des médiathèques</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Télécharge des illustrations pour les séries télé, les films et les vidéos musicales dans votre vidéothèque</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Descargue na súa biblioteca Ilustracións para as Series de TV, Filmes e Vídeos Musicais</summary>
    <summary lang="he">הורדת גרפיקה לסדרות, סרטים וקליפים שבספריית המדיה</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Preuzimte slike omota TV serija, filmova i glazbenih spotova u vašoj kolekciji</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Művészképek letöltése TV műsorok, filmek és videóklipek számára</summary>
    <summary lang="id">Unduh Artwork for acara TC, Film and Video musik di perpustakaan anda</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Scarica Artwork per Serie TV, Film e Video Musicali della tua Libreria</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">라이브러리의 TV 쇼, 영화, 뮤직비디오의 아트워크 다운로드</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Atsiunčia iliustracijas TV laidoms, filmams ir muzikiniams vaizdo klipams, esantiems jūsų bibliotekoje</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Download Artwork voor TV series, Films en Muziekvideos in jouw bibliotheek</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Last ned illustrasjoner til TV-serier, filmer og musikkvideoer i biblioteket ditt</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Pobiera grafiki dla seriali, filmów i teledysków znajdujący się w Twojej bibliotece</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Transfira Artwork de Séries TV, Filmes e Videoclipes para a sua biblioteca</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Transferências Artes de Seriados, Filmes e Concertos para suas Coleções.</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Загрузка обложек для сериалов, фильмов и клипов в Вашу медиатеку.</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Sťahuje umeleckú grafiku k TV seriálom, filmom a hudobným videám vo Vašej knižnici</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Laddar ner bilder och extramaterial för TV-serierna, filmerna och musikvideorna i ditt bibliotek</summary>
    <summary lang="zh">下载剧集、电影和音乐电视艺术图片到资料库</summary>
    <description lang="be">Downloads all available artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library. Check the options for supported artwork[CR]Artwork sources:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Remark:[CR]Check your skin to see what type of artwork is supported![CR]Each TV Show/Movie must have its own folder![CR]Skin integration:[CR]See readme file</description>
    <description lang="bg">Сваля всички налични изображения за филми, ТВ Сериали и музикални клипове от библиотеката ви. Проверете настройките за поддържаните типове изображения. [CR]Източници:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Забележка:[CR]Проверете какъв тип изображения поддържа ползвания от вас облик![CR]Всеки филм / ТВ Сериал трябва да бъде в отделна папка![CR]За интегриране в облици:[CR]Прочетете файла "readme"</description>
    <description lang="ca">Descarrega totes les il·lustracions disponibles per a sèries de TV, pel·lícules i vídeos musicals a la seva biblioteca. Revisi les opcions per donart suport[CR] a les fonts d'il·lustracions:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Avís:[CR]Comprova quin tipus de il·lustracions suporta la teva Pell![CR]Cada sèries de TV/pel·lícula té que tindre la seva pròpia carpeta![CR]Integració amb Pells:[CR]Llegeix el fitxer readme</description>
    <description lang="cs">Stáhne všechny dostupné artworky pro seriály, filmy a hudební videa ve vaší knihovně. Nastav možnosti pro podporované artworky.&#10;artwork[CR]Zdroje artworků:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Poznámkak:[CR]Zkontrolu si jaký typ artworků podporuje tvůj skin![CR]Každý seriál/film musí mít svoji vlastní složku![CR]Integrace do skinu:[CR]Podívej se do readme souboru</description>
    <description lang="da">Henter alle tilgængelige illustrationer til TV-serier, Film og Musikvideoer i dit bibliotek. Tjek indstillingerne for at se understøttede illustrationer.[CR]Kilder til illustrationer[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Bemærk:[CR]Tjek dit skin for at se, hvilke typer illustrationer, der understøttes![CR]Hver TV-serie/Film skal have sin egen mappe![CR]Skin-integration:[CR]Se 'readme' fil</description>
    <description lang="de">Downloadet alle verfügbaren Artworks für TV Sendungen, Filme und Musikvideos in deine Datenbank. Überprüfe die Optionen für nicht unterstützte Artwork[CR]Artworkquellen: [CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Remark:[CR]Überprüfe dein Skin ob Artwork unterstützt wird![CR]Jede TV Sendung/Film braucht seinen eigenen Ordner![CR]Skin Integration:[CR]Siehe Readme Datei</description>
    <description lang="el">Κατεβάζει όλες τις διαθέσιμες εικόνες για τις Τηλεοπτικές Σειρές, τις Ταινίες και τα Μουσικά Βίντεο της συλλογής σας. Ελέγξτε τις επιλογές για υποστηριζόμενες εικόνες[CR]&#10;Πηγές Εικόνων:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]&#10;Σημείωση:[CR]Ελέγξτε το κέλυφός σας για να δείτε τι είδους εικόνες υποστηρίζονται![CR]Κάθε Σειρά/Ταινία πρέπει να έχει το δικό της φάκελο![CR]&#10;Για ενσωμάτωση στο κέλυφος:[CR]Δείτε το αρχείο readme</description>
    <description lang="en">Downloads all available artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library. Check the options for supported artwork[CR]Artwork sources:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Remark:[CR]Check your skin to see what type of artwork is supported![CR]Each TV Show/Movie must have its own folder![CR]Skin integration:[CR]See readme file</description>
    <description lang="en_AU">Downloads all available artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library. Check the options for supported artwork[CR]Artwork sources:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Remark:[CR]Check your skin to see what type of artwork is supported![CR]Each TV Show/Movie must have its own folder![CR]Skin integration:[CR]See readme file</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Downloads all available artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library. Check the options for supported artwork[CR]Artwork sources:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Remark:[CR]Check your skin to see what type of artwork is supported![CR]Each TV Show/Movie must have its own folder![CR]Skin integration:[CR]See readme file</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Downloads all available artwork for TV shows, Movies and Musicvideos in your library. Check the options for supported artwork[CR]Artwork sources:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Remark:[CR]Check your skin to see what type of artwork is supported![CR]Each TV Show/Movie must have its own folder![CR]Skin integration:[CR]See readme file</description>
    <description lang="es">Descarga artwork de programas de televisión, películas y vídeos musicales en tu biblioteca. Marca las opciones correspondientes[CR]Fuentes de artwork:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Aviso:[CR]Comprueba qué tipo de artwork soporta tu skin![CR]Cada show de TV y película debe tener su propia carpeta![CR]Integración de skin:[CR]Consulta el archivo Léame</description>
    <description lang="fr">Ce collecteur permet de télécharger toutes les illustration disponibles pour les séries TV, les films et les clips vidéo de toutes les médiathèques. Voir les options pour les illustrations gérées.[CR]Sources des illustrations :[CR]- www.fanart.tv[CR]- www.thetvdb.com[CR]- www.themoviedb.org[CR][CR]NB : vérifier le thême pour savoir quel type d'illustration est reconnu ![CR]Chaque Série TV / Film doit avoir son propre dossier ![CR]Intégration dans un thême : voir le fichier « readme.txt ».</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Télécharge toutes les illustrations disponibles pour les émissions télé, les films et les vidéos musicales dans votre vidéothèque. Vérifiez les options pour les illustrations prisent en charge[CR]Sources d'illustrations :&#10;[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Remarque :[CR]Vérifiez votre habillage pour voir quel type d'illustrations est pris en charge[CR]Chaque série télé/film doit avoir son propre dossier![CR]Intégration à l'habillage :[CR]Consultez le fichier readme</description>
    <description lang="gl">Descarga todas as ilustracións dispoñíbeis para as series de TV, filmes e vídeos musicais da súa biblioteca. Verifique as opcións de soporte de ilustracións[CR]Fontes das ilustracións:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Lembre:[CR]Verifique o seu tema para ver que tipo de ilustración é soportada.[CR]Cada Serie de TV/Filme debe ter o seu propio cartafol.[CR]Integración no tema:[CR]Ver o ficheiro readme</description>
    <description lang="he">הורדת כל סוגי הגרפיקה הזמינה עבור סדרות, סרטים וקליפים שבספריית המדיה. ניתן לסקור באפשרויות ההרחבה את סוגי הגרפיקה להורדה.[CR]מקורות גרפיקה:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]הערות:[CR]יש לבדוק איזה סוג גרפיקה נתמכת ע"י המעטפת המותקנת![CR]לכל סדרה/סרט חייבת להיות תיקיה ייחודיתו![CR]שילוב במעטפת:[CR]יש לפנות לקובץ readme</description>
    <description lang="hr">Preuzmi sve dostupne slike omota za TV serije, filmove i glazbene spotove u vašoj zbirci. Provjerite mogućnosti za podržane slike omota[CR]Izvori slika omota:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Napomena:[CR]Provjerite vašu presvlaku da bi vidjeli koja vrsta presvlake je podržana![CR]Svaka TV serija/Film mora imati svoju vlastitu mapu![CR]Integracija presvlake:[CR]Pogledajte datoteku uputa</description>
    <description lang="hu">Letölti az összes rendelkezésre álló művészképet az adatbázisában található TV-műsorokhoz, filmekhez és videóklipekhez. Ellenőrizze a beállításokat a támogatott művészképekhez[CR]Művészkép források:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Megjegyzés:[CR]Ellenőrizze, hogy az alkalmazott skin miyen művészképeket támogat![CR]Minden filmnek/TV-műsornak saját mappában kell lennie![CR]Skin integráció:[CR]Olvassa fel a readme fájlt</description>
    <description lang="it">Scarica tutti gli Artwork disponibili per le Serie TV, i Film ed i Video Musicali presenti nella Libreria. Controlla le opzioni per gli Artwork supportati[CR]Fonti Artwork:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Nota:[CR]Controlla la tua Skin per vedere che tipi di Artwork sono supportati![CR]Ogni Serie TV/Film deve avere una cartella propria![CR]Integrazione Skin:[CR]Vedi file readme</description>
    <description lang="ko">라이브러리에 있는 TV 쇼, 영화, 뮤직비디오의 사용 가능한 모든 아트워크를 다운로드합니다. 지원하는 아트워크는 옵션을 확인하세요[CR]아트워크 소스:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR] 참고:[CR]사용하는 스킨이 어떤 형식의 아트워크를 지원하는지 확인하세요![CR]각 TV 쇼/영화는 자신의 폴더에 있어야 합니다![CR]스킨 통합:[CR]readme 파일 참고</description>
    <description lang="lt">Atsiunčia visas prieinamas iliustracijas TV laidoms, filmams ir muzikiniams vaizdo klipams, esantiems jūsų bibliotekoje. Palaikomus iliustracijų tipus galite rasti parinktyse.[CR]Iliustracijų šaltiniai:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Pastaba:[CR]Pasitikrinkite kokius iliustracijos tipus palaiko jūsų teminė išvaizda![CR]KiekvienaTV laida/filmas turi būti atskirame aplanke![CR]Teminės išvaizdos integracija:[CR]Žiūrėkite 'readme' failą</description>
    <description lang="nl">Download alle beschikbare artwork voor TV series, Films en Muziekvideos in jouw bibliotheek. Bekijk de opties voor ondersteunde artwork[CR]Artwork bronnen:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Opmerking:[CR]Controleer jouw skin om te bepalen welke artwork deze ondersteund![CR]Elke TV serie/Film moet zich in zijn eigen folder bevinden![CR]Skin integratie:[CR]Kijk in de readme bestand</description>
    <description lang="no">Last ned alle tilgjengelige illustrasjoner til TV-serier, filmer og musikkvideoer i ditt bibliotek. Se alternativene for støttede illustrasjoner[CR]Illustrasjonskilder:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Bemerk:[CR]Sjekk ditt skall for å se hvilken type illustrasjoner som er støttet![CR]Hver TV-serie/film må ha sin egen mappe![CR]Skallintegrasjon:[CR]Sjekk lesmeg-filen</description>
    <description lang="pl">Dodatek ten pozwala na pobieranie wszystkich dostępnych grafik dla seriali, filmów i teledysków w Twojej bibliotece. Sprawdź ustawienia, aby zobaczyć wszystkie dostępne rodzaje grafik.[CR]&#10;Źródła grafik:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Uwaga:[CR]Sprawdź jakie rodzaje grafik wspiera twoja skóra![CR]Każdy serial/film musi być w osobnym folderze![CR]Integracja ze skórą:[CR]Przeczytaj plik readme&#10;    </description>
    <description lang="pt">Transfere toda a artwork disponível para Séries TV, Filmes e Vídeoclipes na sua biblioteca. Verifique a artwork suportada nas opções.[CR]Fontes de Artwork:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Lembre-se:[CR]Verifique o seu tema para ver que tipo de artwork é suportada![CR]Cada Série TV/Filme deve ter a sua própria pasta![CR]Integração no tema:[CR]veja o ficheiro readme</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Download todas as artworks disponíveis para Seriados, Filmes e Concertos em sua coleção. Verifique as opções de artes suportadas. &#10;Artwork fontes:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]Lembrete:[CR]Verifique se sua skin tem suporte para os tipos de artes disponíveis![CR]Cada Seriado/Filme ou Concerto deve estar em pastas próprias![CR]Skin integração:[CR]Veja o arquivo leia-me.</description>
    <description lang="sk">Sťahuje umeleckú grafiku k TV seriálom, filmom a hudobným videám vo Vašej knižnici. Na overenie podporovanej umeleckej grafiky pozrite nastavenia.&#10;Zdroje umeleckej grafiky:&#10;www.fanart.tv&#10;www.thetvdb.com&#10;www.themoviedb.org&#10;Poznámka:&#10;Aby ste si overili aká umelecká grafika je podporovaná, skontrolujte Váš Vzhľad!&#10;Každý TV seriál / film musí byť v samostatnom priečinku!&#10;Integrácia so vzhľadom:&#10;Pozri readme súbor</description>
    <description lang="sv">Laddar ner alla tillgängliga omslag, bakgrunder etc för TV-serier, Filmer och Musikvideos till ditt bibliotek. Kontrollera inställningar för vad som stöds[CR] Omslag, bakgrunder etc hämtas från följande resurser:[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR] Remark:[CR]Kontrollera skalinställningar för att ta reda på vad som stöds![CR]Varje TV-serie/Film måste ha sin egen mapp![CR] Skalintegration:[CR]See readme file</description>
    <description lang="zh">下载剧集、电影和音乐电视的所有可用艺术图片到资料库。查看支持的艺术图片选项[CR]&#10;艺术图片来源：[CR]www.fanart.tv[CR]www.thetvdb.com[CR]www.themoviedb.org[CR]&#10; 备注：[CR]查看你的皮肤了解支持什么类型的艺术图片！[CR]每一个剧集/电影必须保存在单独的文件夹中！[CR]&#10; 皮肤集成：[CR]参见readme文件</description>
    <disclaimer lang="be">For bugs, requests or general questions visit the Artwork Downloader thread on the Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="bg">За грешки, заявки и общи въпроси посетете темата на Artwork Downloader във форума на Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ca">Per errors, peticions o preguntes en general visiteu el fil de Artwork Downloader en el fòrum de Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="cs">Kvůli chybám, požadavkům nebo obecným dotazům navštivte Artwork Downloader vlákno na forů Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="da">Ved fejl, forespørgsler eller generelle spørgsmål besøg Artwork Downloader-tråden i Kodis forum.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="de">Für Fehler, Vorschläge oder allgemeine Fragen, besuchen Sie das Artwork Downloader-Thema im Kodi-Forum (englisch).</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="el">Για προβλήματα, αιτήματα ή γενικές ερωτήσεις επισκεφθείτε το θέμα του Artwork Downloader στο forum του Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en">For bugs, requests or general questions visit the Artwork Downloader thread on the Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_AU">For bugs, requests or general questions visit the Artwork Downloader thread on the Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">For bugs, requests or general questions visit the Artwork Downloader thread on the Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="en_US">For bugs, requests or general questions visit the Artwork Downloader thread on the Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="es">Para informar de errores, hacer peticiones o preguntas visiten el hilo Artwork Downloader en el foro de Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr">Pour les bogues, demandes ou questions générales visiter le fil Artwork Downloader sur le forum Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Pour les bogues, les demandes et les questions générales, visitez le fil « Artwork downloader » sur le forum Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="gl">Para erros, solicitudes ou preguntas en xeral visite o fio do Artwork Downloader no foro do Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="he">לדווח על תקלות, בקשות או שאלות כלליות יש לבקר בשרשור של Artwork Downloader בפורום Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hr">Za greške, zahtjeve ili uobičajena pitanja posjetite Artwork Downloader na Kodi forumu.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="hu">Hibabejelentéshez, kérésekhez vagy általános kérdésekkel kapcsolatban keresse az Artwork Downloader témát az Kodi fórumon.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="it">Per la segnalazione di bug, richieste o domande generali visita il thread Artwork Downloader sul forum di Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ko">버그, 요청사항 및 일반적인 질문은  Kodi 포럼의 Artwork Downloader 글타래를 찾아 주세요.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="lt">Jei norite pranešti apie klaidą, turite pageidavimų ar šiaip norite paklausti, apsilankykite Kodi forumo Artwork Downloader gijoje.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="nl">Voor fouten, verzoeken of algemene vragen kan je terecht op Artwork Downloader thread op het Kodi forum.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="no">For «bugs», anmodninger og generelle spørsmål, besøk Artwork Downloader-tråden på Kodi-forumet.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pl">W celu zgłoszenia błędu, prośby lub zadania pytania, odwiedź temat poświęcony dodatkowi Artwork Downloader na forum Kodi. </disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt">Para reportar erros, requisitar algo ou perguntar algo sobre o add-on, visite o tópico do Artwork Downloader no fórum do Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Para erros, requisições ou questões gerais visite o tópico do Artwork Downloader no Fórum Kodi.tv</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="ru">По всем ошибкам, пожеланиям и общим вопросам посетите топик Artwork Downloader на форуме Kodi.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sk">Pre chyby, požiadavky alebo všeobecné otázky navštívte "Artwork Downloader" vlákno na Kodi fóre.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="sv">För buggar, önskemål och frågor, besök Artwork Downloader tråden på Kodis forum.</disclaimer>
    <disclaimer lang="zh">错误报告、功能需求及常见问题，请访问Kodi论坛的Artwork Downloader专贴。</disclaimer>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <forum>http://forum.xbmc.org/showthread.php?tid=114633</forum>
    <website></website>
    <email></email>
    <source>https://github.com/XBMC-Addons/script.artwork.downloader</source>
  </extension>
</addon>
