<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<addon id="skin.arctic" version="0.6.7" name="Arctic" provider-name="jurialmunkey">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.gui" version="4.0.0" />
		<import addon="service.skin.widgets" version="0.0.25" />
		<import addon="script.artwork.downloader" version="12.0.15" />
		<import addon="script.tv.show.next.aired" version="5.0.7" />
		<import addon="script.tvtunes" version="3.0.6" />
		<import addon="script.favourites" version="4.0.9" />
		<import addon="script.artistslideshow" version="1.5.0" />
		<import addon="script.videolanguage" version="0.1.0" />
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.gui.skin" defaultthemename="Textures.xbt" effectslowdown="1.00" debugging="false">
		<res width="1920" height="1080" aspect="16:9" default="true" folder="1080i" />
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="de">Arctic ist ein leichtgewichtiger Skin mit Fokus auf Schlichtheit</summary>
        <summary lang="el">Το Arctic είναι ένα ελαφρύ θέμα που δίνει έμφαση στην απλότητα.</summary>
        <summary lang="en">Arctic is a light skin that focuses on simplicity</summary>
        <summary lang="en_AU">Arctic is a light skin that focuses on simplicity</summary>
        <summary lang="en_NZ">Arctic is a light skin that focuses on simplicity</summary>
        <summary lang="en_US">Arctic is a light skin that focuses on simplicity</summary>
        <summary lang="es">Arctic es un skin liviano que se centra en la simplicidad</summary>
        <summary lang="fi">Arctic on kevyt ja yksinkertainen ulkoasu</summary>
        <summary lang="fr">Arctic est un skin léger qui se concentre sur la simplicité</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_CA">Artic est habillage léger qui cible la simplicité</summary>
        <summary lang="hu">Az Arctic egy könnyed felszín ami az egyszerűségre koncentrál</summary>
        <summary lang="it">Artic è una skin leggera che si concentra sulla semplicità</summary>
        <summary lang="ko">Arctic 은 단순함에 중점을 둔 가벼운 스킨입니다.</summary>
        <summary lang="lt">Arctic yra šviesi teminė išvaizda katra orientuota į paprastumą</summary>
        <summary lang="ms">Artic merupakan kulit yang ringan ia menjurus ke arah ringkas</summary>
        <summary lang="nl">Arctic is een lichte skin dat zich focust op eenvoudigheid.</summary>
        <summary lang="pl">Arctic to lekka skóra, skupiona na prostocie</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_BR">Arctic é uma skin leve com foco na simplicidade.</summary>
        <summary lang="ru">Arctic - это лёгкая и простая обложка для XBMC </summary>
        <summary lang="sv">Arctic är ett skal som fokuserar på enkelhet</summary>
        <summary lang="th">Arctic เป็นสกินเบาๆ ที่เน้นความเรียบง่าย</summary>
        <summary lang="zh">Arctic是个专注于简洁的轻量化皮肤</summary>
        <description lang="de">Arctic ist ursprünglich eine Modifikation des Blacks Xperience1080-Skins, die Einflüsse des Alaska-Skins einfliessen ließ. &#10;Mittlerweile ist daraus ein eigenständiger Skin mit Fokus auf Schlichtheit, Eleganz und einer Vielzahl von Ansichtsoptionen entstanden.</description>
        <description lang="el">Το Arctic ξεκίνησε σαν μετατροπή (mod) με σκοπό το συνδυασμό του κελύφους Alaska με το xperience1080 του 'Black. Έκτοτε έχει εξελιχθεί σε ένα πλήρες κέλυφος, το οποίο εστιάζει κυρίως στην απλότητα, την κομψότητα και την παροχή μιας πληθώρας επιλογών προβολής.</description>
        <description lang="en">Arctic originally began as a modification seeking to bring an Alaska influence to Black's xperience1080 skin. It has since evolved into a skin of its own - focusing on simplicity, elegance and providing multiple view options.</description>
        <description lang="en_AU">Arctic originally began as a modification seeking to bring an Alaska influence to Black's xperience1080 skin. It has since evolved into a skin of its own - focusing on simplicity, elegance and providing multiple view options.</description>
        <description lang="en_NZ">Arctic originally began as a modification seeking to bring an Alaska influence to Black's xperience1080 skin. It has since evolved into a skin of its own - focusing on simplicity, elegance and providing multiple view options.</description>
        <description lang="en_US">Arctic originally began as a modification seeking to bring an Alaska influence to Black's xperience1080 skin. It has since evolved into a skin of its own - focusing on simplicity, elegance and providing multiple view options.</description>
        <description lang="es">Arctic inicialmente comenzó como una modificación parar un toque Alaska al skin xperience1080. Desde entonces ha evolucionado en un skin en sí mismo, enfocado en la simplicidad y elegancia, ofreciendo múltiples opciones de visualización.</description>
        <description lang="fi">Arcticin kehitys alkoi Blackin xperience1080-ulkoasun muokkaamisella. Se on sittemmin kehittynyt aivan omanlaisekseen ulkoasuksi - selkeä, elegantti ja useita eri näkymävaihtoehtoja.</description>
        <description lang="fr">Arctic débuta par une touche d'influence d'Alaska au skin xperience1080 de Black. Il a depuis évolué en un skin à part entière, centré sur la simplicité, l'élégance et fournit de nombreuses options de vues.</description>
        <description lang="fr_CA">Artic a d'abord commencé comme une modification cherchant a apporter l'influence d'Alaska à l'habillage Xperience1080 de Black. Depuis il a évolué en un habillage à part entière, ciblant la simplicité, l'élégance et fournissant plusieurs options d'affichage.</description>
        <description lang="hu">Az Arctic eredetileg egy  Black's xperience1080 felszín változatként kezdte ami az Alaszkai érzést hozza. Azóta önálló felszínné nőtte ki magát - az egyszerűségre, eleganciára és a többfajta nézet lehetőségére fókuszálva.</description>
        <description lang="it">Artic è nata originariamente come una modifica per portare l'ecosistema di Alaska sulla skin Black's xperience1080. Da allora si è evoluta in una skin a se stante - che si concentra sulla semplicità, l'eleganza e l'offerta di diverse opzioni di visualizzazione.</description>
        <description lang="ko">Arctic 은 Black 이 제작한 Xperience 1080 스킨에 Alaska 스킨의 접목을 추구하던 수정판에서 시작되었습니다. 지금은 단순함, 우아함, 다양한 보기 옵션에 중점을 두는 독자적인 스킨이 되기에 이르렀습니다.</description>
        <description lang="lt">Arctic iš pradžių įtakojo siekį integruotis paraleliai 'Aliaska' teminės išvaizdos Black xperience 1080 teminėje išvaizdoje. Nuo to laiko išsivystė į savo teminę išvaizdą - sutelkiant dėmesį į paprastumą, eleganciją bei teikia kelias smulkias galimybes.</description>
        <description lang="ms">Artic pada asalnya bermula dari pengubahsuaian untuk ketengahkan pengaruh Alaska ke kulit xperience1080. Semenjak itu ia telah berubah menjadi kulit mengikut temanya sendiri - berfokuskan pada keringkasan, elegen dan menyediakan pilihan paparan berbilang.</description>
        <description lang="nl">Arctic begon origineel door een modificatie te zoeken om een Alaska invloed te brengen naar Black`s Xperience1080 ontwerp. sindsdien is het geëvolueerd tot een eigen skin - het focust zich op gemakkelijkheid, elegantie en verstrekt meervoudige kijk opties.</description>
        <description lang="pt_BR">Arctic começou originalmente como uma modificação, buscando trazer a skin Alaska uma influencia da da skin Xperience1080. Evoluiu então para uma skin própria - focando na simplicidade, elegância e oferecendo muitas opções de visualização.</description>
        <description lang="ru">Arctic начинался как модификация в попытке объединить Alaska и xperience1080. В процессе Arctic превратился в самостоятельную обложку, в которой основное внимание уделено простоте, изяществу и многочисленным режимам просмотра.</description>
        <description lang="sv">Arctic påbörjades för att ge en Alaska-influerad modifiering till Black's Xperience1080 skal. Det har sedan dess evolverat till ett eget skal - med fokus enkelhet, elegans och tillhandahålla flervy-alternativ.</description>
        <description lang="zh">Arctic最初是Black的xperience 1080皮肤的修改版本，并受到皮肤Alaska的影响。现在它已经独成一体 - 专注于简洁，优雅，并提供多种视图选项。</description>
        <disclaimer lang="bg">Съвместим само с XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="cs">Kompatibilní pouze s XBMC 12.x "Frodo"</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de">Nur kompatibel mit XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="el">Συμβατό μόνο με την έκδοση XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en">Compatible with XBMC 12.x "Frodo" only.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_AU">Compatible with XBMC 12.x "Frodo" only.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_NZ">Compatible with XBMC 12.x "Frodo" only.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_US">Compatible with XBMC 12.x "Frodo" only.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es">Solo compatible con XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fi">Toimii vain XBMC-versiossa 12.x (Frodo).</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr">Compatible avec XBMC 12.x "Frodo" uniquement.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr_CA">Compatible seulement avec XBMC 12.x « Frodo ».</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="gl">Solo compatible con XBMC 12.x "Frodo"</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="he">תומך בגירסת "פרודו" XMBC 12.x בלבד</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="hu">Csak az XBMC 12.x "Frodo"-val kompatibilis</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="it">Compatibile solo con XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ko">XBMC 12.x "Frodo"에서만 사용할 수 있습니다.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="lt">Suderinama tik su XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ms">Serasi dengan XBMC 12.x "Frodo" sahaja.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="nl">Alleen compatibel met XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pl">Skóra kompatybilna wyłącznie z XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt">Compatível apenas com o XBMC 12.x "Frodo"</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="pt_BR">Compatível somente com XBMC 12.0 "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ru">Совместим только с последними сборками XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="sv">Endast kompatibel med XBMC 12.x "Frodo"</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="th">รองรับ XBMC 12.x "Frodo" เท่านั้น.</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh">只兼容于 XBMC 12.x "Frodo".</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>Creative Commons Attribution-Noncommercial-Share Alike 3.0</license>
        <forum>..</forum>
        <email>..</email>
        <source>..</source>
	</extension>
</addon>
