<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='yes'?>
<addon id="plugin.video.vimeo" name="Vimeo" provider-name="TheCollective" version="3.5.3">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0" />
    <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="2.5.2" />
    <import addon="script.module.parsedom" version="2.5.1" />
    <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="1.9.4" />
  </requires>
  <extension library="default.py" point="xbmc.python.pluginsource">
        <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="bg">Видео добавка за Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="ca">Plugin de video Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="cs">Modul videa Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="cy">Ategyn fideo Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="da">Vimeo video plug-in</summary>
    <summary lang="de">Vimeo-Videoplugin</summary>
    <summary lang="el">Plugin βίντεο Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="en">Vimeo video plugin</summary>
    <summary lang="en_NZ">Vimeo video plugin</summary>
    <summary lang="en_US">Vimeo video plugin</summary>
    <summary lang="es">Plugin de video de Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="es_AR">Plugin de video Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="et">Vimeo video plugin</summary>
    <summary lang="fi">Vimeo-videoliitännäinen</summary>
    <summary lang="fr">Plugin vidéo Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="fr_CA">Plugiciel vidéo pour Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="gl">Engadido de vídeo de Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="he">תוסף וידאו מ־Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="hr">Vimeo video dodatak</summary>
    <summary lang="hu">Vimeo videó kiegészítő</summary>
    <summary lang="it">Plugin Video Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="ja">Vimeo ビデオプラグイン</summary>
    <summary lang="ko">Vimeo 비디오 플러그인</summary>
    <summary lang="lt">Vimeo vaizdo įrašų priedas</summary>
    <summary lang="lv">Vimeo video spraudnis</summary>
    <summary lang="mk">Vimeo додаток за видеа</summary>
    <summary lang="ms">Pemalam video Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="my">Viemo ဗီဒီယို plugin</summary>
    <summary lang="nl">Vimeo videoplugin</summary>
    <summary lang="no">Vimeo video plugin</summary>
    <summary lang="pl">Wtyczka wideo Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="pt">Plugin de vídeo Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="pt_BR">Plugin de vídeo do Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="ro">Extensie video Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="ru">Видео-плагин Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="sk">Vimeo video doplnok</summary>
    <summary lang="sl">Video vtičnik Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="sv">Vimeo videotillägg</summary>
    <summary lang="ta_IN">Vimeo வீடியோ செருகுநிரல்</summary>
    <summary lang="tr">Vimeo video eklentisi</summary>
    <summary lang="uk">Відео модуль Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="uz">Vimeo video plagini</summary>
    <summary lang="vi">Plugin cho dịch vụ chia sẻ video Vimeo</summary>
    <summary lang="vi_VN">Tiện ích video vimeo </summary>
    <summary lang="zh">Vimeo视频插件</summary>
    <summary lang="zh_TW">Vimeo視頻外掛插件</summary>
    <description lang="bg">Добавката ви позволява да разглеждате и гледате видео клипове от любимия на всички алтернативен видео сайт!</description>
    <description lang="ca">Plugin que et permet buscar i veure vídeos del lloc web de vídeos alternativa preferida de tot el món!</description>
    <description lang="cs">Modul, který vám umožní procházet a přehrávat videa z nejoblíbenější alternativní stránky videí.</description>
    <description lang="cy">Ategyn sy'n caniatáu i chi bori a chwarae fideos o hoff wefan fideo arall pawb!</description>
    <description lang="da">Plugin som giver dig mulighed for at udforske og se videoer fra alles foretrukne side for alternative videoer!</description>
    <description lang="de">Dieses Plugin ermöglicht das Durchsuchen und Wiedergeben der Videos von Vimeo!</description>
    <description lang="el">Ένα plugin που σας επιτρέπει να περιηγηθείτε και να δείτε βίντεο από την πιο αγαπημένη εναλλακτική ιστοσελίδα βίντεο!</description>
    <description lang="en">Plugin that allows you to browse and view videos from everybodys favorite alternative video site!</description>
    <description lang="en_NZ">Plugin that allows you to browse and view videos from everybodys favorite alternative video site!</description>
    <description lang="en_US">Plugin that allows you to browse and view videos from everybodys favorite alternative video site!</description>
    <description lang="es">Plugin que te permite navegar y ver videos desde el sitio alternativo favorito de todo el mundo!</description>
    <description lang="es_AR">Plugin que permite listar y ver videos del sitio de videos alternativo que gusta a todo el mundo</description>
    <description lang="et">Plugin, mis võimaldab sul sirvida ja vaadata videosid kõikide lemmik alternatiivsel video saidil!</description>
    <description lang="fr">Plugin qui vous permet d'explorer et de regarder les vidéos des sites de streaming alternatifs!</description>
    <description lang="fr_CA">Plugiciel vous permettant de naviguer et des visionner des vidéos du site alternatif favori de tous!</description>
    <description lang="gl">Engadido que permite explorar e reproducir vídeos do sitio alternativo favorito de todos!</description>
    <description lang="he">תוסף המאפשר לך לעיין ולצפות בסרטוני וידאו מאתר הווידאו החלופי המועדף על כולם!</description>
    <description lang="hr">Dodatak koji vam omogućuje pregledavanje i reprodukciju videa sa alternativnih omiljenih video stranica!</description>
    <description lang="hu">A kiegészítő segítségével videókat böngészhetsz és játszhatsz le mindenki kedvenc alternatív videó oldaláról!</description>
    <description lang="it">Plugin che permette di sfogliare e vedere video dal sito alternativo preferito di tutti il video!</description>
    <description lang="ja">みんなの大好きな代わりのビデオサイトからビデオをブラウズして再生することができるプラグインです！</description>
    <description lang="ko">비메오의 동영상을 탐색하고 재생할 수 있는 플러그인</description>
    <description lang="lt">Įskiepis leidžia naršyti ir žiūrėti vaizdo įrašus iš visų mėgstamo alternatyvaus vaizdo įrašų tinklapio!</description>
    <description lang="mk">Додаток кој ви овозможува да прелистувате и гледате видеа од сајтот Vimeo</description>
    <description lang="ms">Pemalam yang membolehkan anda layar dan lihat video dari laman video alternatif kegemaran semua orang!</description>
    <description lang="my">မည်သူမဆို မိမိနှစ်သက်ရာ ဗီဒီရို site မှ ရုပ်ရှင်များကို browse လုပ်ခြင်းနှင့် ကြည့်ခြင်းများကို plugin က ခွင့်ပြုပေးထားသည်။</description>
    <description lang="nl">Plugin waarmee je video's kunt zoeken en bekijken van ieders favoriete alternatieve videosite! </description>
    <description lang="no">Plugin som lar deg bla gjennom og se filmer fra alles favoritt alternative video side!</description>
    <description lang="pl">Wtyczka pozwala na wyszukiwanie i oglądanie wideo z ulubionej przez wszystkich alternatywnej strony wideo!</description>
    <description lang="pt">Um plugin que permite navegar e ver vídeos no site alternativo que todos adoram.</description>
    <description lang="pt_BR">Plugin que permite que você navegue e veja vídeos do site alternativo de vídeos favorito de todo mundo!</description>
    <description lang="ro">Extensie care îți permite să răsfoiești și să vizualizezi videoclipuri de pe site-ul video alternativ iubit de toată lumea!</description>
    <description lang="ru">Плагин который позволяет просматривать видео с лучшего альтернативного видео сайта!</description>
    <description lang="sk">Doplnok, ktorý umožňuje prehliadanie a pozeranie videí z obľúbenej alternatívnej vide stránky!</description>
    <description lang="sl">Vtični, ki vam omogoča brskanje in predvajanje posnetkov na vsakomur priljubljeni alternativni strani s posnetki!</description>
    <description lang="sv">Tillägg som låter dig bläddra och visa videor från allas favoritalternativvideosajt!</description>
    <description lang="ta_IN">இந்த செருகுநிரல் மூலம் நீங்கள் எல்லாருக்கும் பிடித்தமான வீடியோ இணையத்தில் இருந்து வீடியோக்களை பார்த்து மற்றும் உலாவ முடியும்</description>
    <description lang="tr">Bu eklenti herkesin favori alternatif video sitesinden videolara bakmanızı ve izlemenizi sağlar.</description>
    <description lang="uk">Додаток, що дозволяє переглядати і програвати відео з найкращої сторінки з відео!</description>
    <description lang="vi">Plugin này cho phép bạn duyệt và xem các video từ dịch vụ chia sẻ video rất được ưa thích khác</description>
    <description lang="vi_VN">Tiện ích này sẽ cho phép bạn lấy và xem những video từ mọi người thay thế trang web</description>
    <description lang="zh">使你能从大家喜爱的视频站点浏览和观看视频的插件！</description>
    <description lang="zh_TW">可以讓您多了一個選擇從人人上傳最愛視頻的影片網站瀏覽及檢視影片的外掛插件</description>
    <language></language>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>
